<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 Ryan Lerch <rlerch@redhat.com> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.xfce.thunar</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">thunar.desktop</launchable>
  <name>Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Thunar 檔案管理員</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">Thunar 檔案管理員</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="vec">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ur">تھنر</name>
  <name xml:lang="ur_PK">تھنر</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">Thunar ھۆججەت باشقۇرغۇچ</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">తునార్</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Тунар</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="si">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਥੰਨਰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="lo">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">투나</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">თუნარი</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ie">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="hy">Thunar նիշք</name>
  <name xml:lang="hye">Thunar նիշք</name>
  <name xml:lang="hy_AM">Thunar նիշք</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa_IR">تونار</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_AU">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="bn">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Thunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">ثونار</name>
  <name xml:lang="am">ቱናር</name>
  <summary>File Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">檔案瀏覽器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">文件浏览器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Trình duyệt Tệp</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vec">Navegador de file</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ug">ھۆججەت كۆرگۈچ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Dosya Tarayıcı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">โปรแกรมค้าหาแฟ้ม</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Filbläddrare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Прегледник датотека</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Shfletues Kartelash</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Datotečni brskalnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správca súborov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Обозреватель файлов</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Explorator de fișiere</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Navegador de Ficheiros</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Navegador de arquivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka plików</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Navegador de fichièrs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Bestandbeheerder</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Filbehandler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lo">ຕົວທ່ອງເບິ່ງໄຟລ໌</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Файлдар шолушысы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ფაილის ბრაუზერი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">ファイルブラウザー</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore di file</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Peramban File</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Fájlkezelő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">סייר קבצים</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xestor de ficheiros</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de fichiers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tiedostoselain</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Failihaldur</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Navegador de archivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">File Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Διαχειριστής αρχείων</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Dateibrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Filbrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Prohlížeč souborů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Navegador de fitxers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Файлов браузър</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Restolador de ficheros</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">متصفح الملفات</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Thunar is a file browser specifically designed for the Xfce Desktop, but also can
      serve as an alternate file browser for other Desktop environments. It has a simple,
      clean two-pane design for browsing all your files.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Thunar 是為 Xfce 桌面設計的檔案瀏覽器，但也可以作為其他桌面環境的替代檔案瀏覽器。它有易用且簡潔的雙窗格設計，讓您瀏覽所有的檔案。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Thunar 是一个专门针对 Xfce 桌面环境设计的文件浏览器，但它也能作为其他桌面环境的替代文件浏览器。它有一个简洁的双栏式设计让您浏览所有的文件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Thunar là một trình duyệt tệp đặc biệt được thiết kế cho Xfce Desktop, nhưng cũng có thể sử dụng như một trình duyệt tệp thay thế cho các giao diện Desktop khác</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Thunar - це переглядач структури файлів, розроблений спеціально для оболонки Xfce, однак також може слугувати як альтернативний переглядач фалів для інших середовищ робочого столу. Він простий, має двопанельний дизайн для показу файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ug">Thunar مەخسۇس Xfce ئۈستەلئۈستى مۇھىتى ئۈچۈن لايىھەلەنگەن ھۆججەت باشقۇرغۇچ ئەمما ئۇ باشقا ئۈستەلئۈستى مۇھىتى ئۈچۈن نامزات ھۆججەت باشقۇرغۇچ سۈپىتىدە ئىشلىتىلسىمۇ بولىدۇ. ئۇنىڭ ھۆججەت باشقۇرىدىغان ئاددىي قوش كۆزنەكچە لايىھەسى بار.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Thunar, özel olarak Xfce Masaüstü için dosya tarayıcısı olarak geliştirilmiş olsa da diğer masaüstü ortamları için de alternatif dosya tarayıcısı olarak kullanılabilir. Dosyalarınızı taramak için iki parçalı basit ve temiz tasarımı vardır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">Thunar เป็นโปรแกรมท่องดูแฟ้มซึ่งออกแบบมาสำหรับเดสก์ท็อป Xfce โดยเฉพาะ แต่ก็สามารถทำงานเป็นโปรแกรมท่องดูแฟ้มทางเลือกสำหรับเดสก์ท็อปอื่นได้ด้วย การออกแบบจะเรียบง่าย ทำงานสองช่องแบบสะอาดตา เพื่อท่องดูแฟ้มทั้งหมดของคุณ</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Thunar är en filhanterare speciellt utformad för Xfce-skrivbordet, men den kan också användas som alternativ filhanterare i andra skrivbordsmiljöer. Den har en enkel tvåpanelsdesign för att bläddra bland alla dina filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Тунар је управник датотека нарочито осмишљен за радно окружење Иксфце, али може и да служи као замена за управника датотека другим радним окружењима. Има једноставан и чист склоп са две површи за управљање датотекама.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Thunar-i është një shfletues kartelash i konceptuar posaçërisht për Desktopin Xfce, por mund të shërbejë si shfletues alternativ kartelash edhe për mjedise të tjerë desktop. Përmban një skemë të thjeshtë, të pastër, me dy kuadrate, për shfletimin e krejt kartelave tuaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Thunar je upravljalnik datotek specifično prilagojen za namizno okolje Xfce, lahko pa ga rabimo tudi kot alternativen brskalnik po datotekah v drugih namiznih okoljih. Ima čist in enostaven dvo-pladenjski videz za brskanje po vseh vaših datotekah.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Thunar je správca súborov navrhnutý špeciálne pre Xfce Desktop, ale možno ho používať aj ako alternatívneho správcu súborov v iných pracovných prostrediach. Ponúka prostý, plne dvoj-panelový vzhľad na prechádzanie všetkých súborov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Thunar — проводник изначально для оболочки Xfce, но может использоваться и в других оболочках. Имеет простой понятный двухпанельный вид для просмотра всех ваших файлов.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Thunar este un explorator de fișiere conceput special pentru mediul grafic de birou Xfce, dar poate servi, de asemenea, ca un explorator de fișiere alternativ pentru alte medii de birou. Acesta are un aspect simplu și curat cu două panouri pentru explorarea tuturor fișierelor dvs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Thunar é um navegador de ficheiros especificamente concebido para o ambiente de trabalho Xfce, mas também pode servir como um navegador de ficheiros alternativo para outros ambientes de trabalho. Tem um design simples de dois painéis para navegar por todos os seus ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Thunar é um navegador de arquivos projetado especificamente para o Desktop Xfce, mas também pode servir como um navegador de arquivos alternativo para outros ambientes de desktop. Ele possui um design simples e limpo, com dois painéis, para navegar por todos os seus arquivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Thunar to przeglądarka plików zaprojektowana specjalnie dla Xfce, ale może również służyć w innych środowiskach graficznych. Ma prostą i czytelną konstrukcję dwupanelową do przeglądania wszystkich plików.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Thunar es un gestionari de fichièrs concebut especificament pel burèu Xfce, mas pòt tanben servir coma gestionari de fichièrs alternatiu per d’autres environaments de burèu. Dispausa d’una interfàcia de dos panèls simpla e epurada per percórrer totes vòstres fichièrs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Thunar er ein filutforskar spesielt utvikla for Xfce-skrivebordet, men han kan òg fungera som ein alternativ utforskar for andre skrivebordsmiljø. Thunar har ei enkel, rein to-panelsutforming for å bla gjennom filene dine. </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Thunar is een bestandbeheerder die specifiek is ontworpen voor de Xfce-werkomgeving, maar hij kan ook dienen als een alternatieve bestandbeheerder in andere werkomgevingen. Hij heeft een eenvoudig, helder dubbelpaneelontwerp om al uw bestanden te kunnen verkennen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Thunar er en filutforsker spesifikt utviklet for Xfce-skrivebordet, men kan også fungere som en alternativ filutforsker for andre skrivebordsmiljø, Den har en simpel, ren to-felts designuttrykk for filene dine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Thunar ialah pelayar fail yang direka khusus untuk Desktop Xfce, tetapi juga bertindak sebagai pelayar fail alternatif untuk persekitaran Desktop lain. Ia mempunyai rekabentuk ringkas, dengan dua-anak-tetingkap yang kemas unntuk pelayaran semua fail anda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Thunar yra, specialiai Xfce Darbalaukiui sukurta, failų tvarkytuvė, tačiau ji gali tarnauti kaip alternatyvi failų tvarkytuvė ir kitose Darbalaukio aplinkose. Ji turi paprastą, tvarkingą dviejų polangių dizainą jūsų visų failų naršymui.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lo">Thunar ເປັນຕົວທ່ອງເບິ່ງໄຟລ໌ທີ່ຖືກອອກແບບມາສະເພາະສຳລັບ Xfce, ແຕ່ກໍສາມາດໃຊ້ເປັນຕົວທ່ອງເບິ່ງໄຟລ໌ທາງເລືອກສຳລັບສະພາບແວດລ້ອມອື່ນໆໄດ້. ມັນມີການອອກແບບທີ່ລຽບງ່າຍ, ສະອາດຕາ ແບບສອງຊ່ອງ ເພື່ອໃຫ້ທ່ອງເບິ່ງໄຟລ໌ທັງໝົດຂອງທ່ານໄດ້ສະດວກ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Thunar는 Xfce 데스크탑을 위해 특별히 설계된 파일 브라우저이지만, 다른 데스크탑 환경에서 대체 파일 브라우저로 사용가능합니다. 모든 파일을 브라우징 할 수있는 간단한 두개의 패널 디자인으로 구성되어있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Thunar - бұл Xfce жұмыс үстелі үшін арнайы жасалған файлдық басқарушы қолданбасы, сонымен қатар, оны басқа да жұмыс үстел орталарында қосымша ретінде қолдануға болады. Оның қарапайым әрі жеңіл екі панельді интерфейсі файлдарды шолу үшін арналған.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Thunar は Xfce デスクトップ環境用に開発されたファイルブラウザーであり、他のデスクトップ環境でも使用できます。シンプルでクリーンな 2 ペインデザインで設計されており、すべてのファイルを閲覧できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Thunar è un gestore di file progettato per l'ambiente Xfce, ma può essere utilizzato come gestore di file alternativo in altri ambienti desktop. Ha un design semplice a due riquadri adatto per sfogliare i propri file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Thunar er skráastjóri sem sérstaklega er hannaður fyrir XFCE-skjáborðið, en se hægt er að nota sem aukaskjástjóra í öðrum skjáborðsumhverfum. Thunar byggist á einfaldri og stílhreinni tveggja-spjalda hönnun til að vafra um skrár og möppur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ie">Thunar es un navigator de files developat specificmen por li ambientie Xfce, ma it anc pote servir quam un navigator alternativ por altri ambienties. It have un simplic e nett dessine con du paneles por navigar vor omni files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Thunar adalah peramban berkas yang dirancang khusus untuk Desktop Xfce, tetapi juga dapat berfungsi sebagai peramban berkas alternatif untuk lingkungan Desktop lainnya. Thunar memiliki desain yang sederhana, desain dua-pane bersih untuk meramban semua berkas Anda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hy">Thunar֊ը նիշային կառավարիչ է, նախագծված հատուկ Xfce աշխատասեղանի համար, բայց այն կարող է ծառայել որպես այլաընտրանքային նիշային կառավարիչ այլ աշխատասեղանի միջավայրերի համար։ Այն ունի պարզ, երկպատուհանավոր տեսք։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hye">Thunar֊ը նիշային կառավարիչ է, նախագծուած հատուկ Xfce աշխատասեղանի համար, բայց այն կարող է ծառայել որպէս այլաընտրանքային նիշային կառավարիչ այլ աշխատասեղանի միջավայրերի համար։ Այն ունի պարզ, երկպատուհանաւոր տեսք։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hy_AM">Thunar֊ը նիշային կառավարիչ է, նախագծուած հատուկ Xfce աշխատասեղանի համար, բայց այն կարող է ծառայել որպէս այլաընտրանքային նիշային կառավարիչ այլ աշխատասեղանի միջավայրերի համար։ Այն ունի պարզ, երկպատուհանաւոր տեսք։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Thunar kifejezetten az Xfce asztali környezethez tervezett fájlkezelő, de más asztali környezetek alternatív fájlkezelőként is szolgál. Egyszerű, tiszta, két táblás felülete van, az összes fájlja tallózásához.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Thunar je upravitelj datotekama posebno dizajniran za Xfce radno okruženje, ali jednako se može koristiti kao alternativni upravitelj datotekama u drugim radnim okruženjima. Posjeduje jednostavan dvokrilni dizajn za sve vaše datoteke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏Thunar הינו סייר קבצים אשר תוכנן בקפידה עבור שולחן עבודה Xfce, אך גם יכול לשרת בתור דפדפן קבצים חלופי עבור סביבות שולחן עבודה אחרות. יש לו עיצוב פשוט, נקי בעל שתי חלוניות לסיור בכל הקבצים שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O Thunar é un xestor de ficheiros deseñado especificamente para o Escritorio XFCE, o cal tamén pode servir como explorador de ficheiros alternativo para outros contornos de escritorio. Este ten un deseño simple con dous paneis para ver todos os seus ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Thunar est un gestionnaire de fichiers conçu spécifiquement pour le bureau Xfce, mais peut aussi servir comme gestionnaire de fichiers alternatif pour d’autres environnements de bureau. Il a une interface à deux panneaux simple et épurée pour parcourir tous vos fichiers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Thunar on tiedostoselain, joka on suunniteltu erityisesti Xfce-työpöydälle, mutta jota voi käyttää vaihtoehtoisena tiedostoselaimena myös muilla työpöytäjärjestelmillä. Se käyttää yksinkertaista kaksiruutuista muotoilua kaikkien tiedostojesi selaamiseen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa_IR">Thunar یک مرورگر پرونده است که به طور خاص برای میز کار Xfce طراحی شده، ولی می‌تواند به عنوان یک مرورگر پروندهٔ جایگزین در سایر میزکارها خدمت‌رسانی کند. آن یک طراحی دو قاب ساده و تمیز برای مرور تمام پرونده‌های شما داد.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Thunar bereziki xfce idazmahairekin erabiltzeko diseinatutako fitxategi kudeatzaile bat da , baina beste mahaigain ingurune batzuekin erabili daiteke, Oso sinplea da, zure fitxategi guztiak kudeatzeko bi paneletako ikuspegi garbiarekin </p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Failihaldur Thunar on loodud Xfce töölaua jaoks, kuid sobib kasutamiseks alternatiivse failihaldurina ka muudes töölauakeskondades. Thunaril on lihtne kahe paaniga vaade kõikide sinu failide haldamise jaoks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Thunar es un navegador de archivos diseñado específicamente para el escritorio Xfce, pero también se puede usar en otros entornos de escritorio. Su diseño de doble panel es sencillo y claro.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Thunar is a file browser specifically designed for the Xfce Desktop, but also can serve as an alternate file browser for other Desktop environments. It has a simple, clean two-pane design for browsing all your files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">Thunar is a file browser specifically designed for the Xfce Desktop, but also can serve as an alternate file browser for other Desktop environments. It has a simple, clean two-pane design for browsing all your files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο Thunar είναι διαχειριστής αρχείων ειδικά σχεδιασμένος για το περιβάλλον εργασίας Xfce, μπορεί όμως να χρησιμοποιηθεί και ως εναλλακτικός διαχειριστής αρχείων σε άλλα περιβάλλοντα εργασίας. Έχει απλή και καθαρή σχεδίαση 2 τμημάτων για τη περιήγηση όλων των αρχείων σας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Thunar ist eine Dateiverwaltung speziell für den Xfce-Schreibtisch entwickelt, kann aber auch als alternativer Dateinavigator für andere Arbeitsumgebungen benutzt werden. Er hat eine einfache, aufgeräumte Zweifensteransicht zum Durchsuchen aller Ihrer Dateien.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Thunar er en filbrowser, specielt designet til Xfce-skrivebordet, men som også bruges som en alternativ filbrowser for andre skrivebordsmiljøer. Den har et simpelt, ryddeligt design med to ruder, til at gennemse dine filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Thunar je správce souborů specificky navržený pro prostředí Xfce, ale může také sloužit jako alternativní aplikace pro procházení souborů v jiných desktopových prostředích. Má jednoduchý čistý dvoupanelový design pro procházení všech Vašich souborů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Thunar és un navegador de fitxers que està dissenyat especialment per a l'escriptori Xfce, però també pot servir com a navegador de fitxers per a altres escriptoris. Té un disseny simple, de dos taulers, per navegar per tots els vostres fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Thunar е приложение за управление на файлове, разработено специално за работната среда Xfce, но може да се използва и в други графични среди. Той е с изчистен двупанелен дизайн за управление на всички ваши файлове.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Thunar - кіраўнік файлаў, распрацаваны для працоўнага асяроддзя Xfce, але таксама можа выкарыстоўвацца ў якасці альтэрнатыўнага кіраўніка файлаў для іншых працоўных асяроддзяў. У яго просты дызайн з магчымасцю двухпанэльнага выгляду для прагляду ўсіх файлаў.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Thunar ye un restolador de ficheros diseñáu específicamente pal escritoriu Xfce, pero tamién pue sirvir como restolador de ficheros alternativu pa otros entornos d'escritoriu. Tien un simple y llimpiu diseñu a dos cares pa restolar tolos tos ficheros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">ثونار متصفح ملفات مصمم خصيصا لسطح مكتب Xfce. لكن يمكن استعماله كتصفح ملفات بديل في بيئات مكتب أخرى. يتميز ثونار بتصميم بسيط يمكنك من تصفح جميع ملفاتك.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://xfce.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/xfce/thunar</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/xfce/thunar/start</url>
  <url type="contact">https://docs.xfce.org/contribute/dev/start#communication_with_the_xfce_development_team</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="759" height="424">https://docs.xfce.org/_media/xfce/thunar/file-manager-window.png</image>
      <caption>Screenshot of the XFCE Thunar File Browser User Interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">XFCE Thunar 檔案瀏覽器使用者介面的螢幕截圖</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">XFCE Thunar 文件浏览器用户界面截图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Hình chụp giao diện của trình duyệt tệp Thunar của XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ug">Thunar ھۆججەت باشقۇرغۇچنىڭ XFCE ئۈستەلئۈستى مۇھىتىدىكى ئىشلەتكۈچى ئارا يۈزىنىڭ ئېكران كەسمىسى</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">XFCE Thunar Dosya Tarayıcı Kullanıcı Arayüzünün Ekran Görüntüsü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="th">ภาพหน้าจอส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้ของโปรแกรมค้นหาแฟ้ม Thunar ของ Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Skärmdump av användargränssnittet för XFCE Thunar filhanterare</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Слика приказа корисничког сучеља прегледника датотека ИксФЦЕ-а Тунара</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sq">Foto ekrani e Ndërfaqes së Përdoruesit të Shfletuesit të Kartelave XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Snímka používateľského rozhrania správcu súborov XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Скриншот пользовательского интерфейса файлового браузера XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Captură de ecran a interfeței gestionarului de fișiere Thunar din XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Captura de ecrã da interface do navegador de ficheiros Thunar do XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Captura de tela da interface do usuário do navegador de arquivos Thunar do XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Zrzut ekranu interfejsu użytkownika przeglądarki plików Xfce Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Captura d’ecran de l’interfàcia utilizaire del gestionari de fichièrs XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Schermafdruk van het uiterlijk van Thunar, de bestandsverkenner van XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Skjermbilde av brukergrensesnittet til filbehandleren Xfce Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lo">ພາບໜ້າຈໍຂອງຕົວຈັດການໄຟລ໌ Thunar ຂອງ XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">XFCE Thunar файлдар басқарушысының пайдаланушы интерфейсінің скриншоты</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">XFCE Thunar ファイルブラウザーユーザーインターフェースのスクリーンショット</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Istantanea dell'interfaccia utente del gestore di file di Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tangkapan layar Antarmuka Pengguna Peramban File XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Képernyőkép az XFCE Thunar fájlkezelő felhasználói felületéről</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">צילום מסך של ממשק משתמש סייר קבצים XFCE Thunar </caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Captura de pantalla da interface de usuario do xestor de ficheiros Thunar do Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Capture d’écran de l’interface utilisateur du navigateur de fichiers Thunar de XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">XFCE Thunari failihalduri kasutajaliidese ekraanitõmmis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Captura de pantalla de la interfaz de usuario del navegador de archivos Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Screenshot of the XFCE Thunar File Browser User Interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Στιγμιότυπο οθόνης του διαχειριστή αρχείων XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Screenshot der Benutzeroberfläche des XFCE Thunar Dateibrowsers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Skærmbillede af brugerfladen i Xfce Filbrowser</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Snímek obrazovky uživatelského rozhraní aplikace Thunar - správce souborů pro XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Captura de pantalla de la interfície d'usuari del navegador de fitxers Thunar de l'XFCE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Екранна снимка на потребителския интерфейс на файловия браузър на XFCE Thunar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لقطة شاشة من واجهة المستخدم لمتصفح الملفات ثونار في أكسفس</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <project_group>Xfce</project_group>
  <update_contact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">Thunar</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
