<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 Eric Koegel <eric.koegel@gmail.com> and Simon Steinbeiß <simon@xfce.org> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.xfce.PowerManager</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Xfce power manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Xfce 電源管理程式</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">Xfce 电源管理器</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Trình quản lý nguồn Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ur">ایکسفس توانائی منیجر</name>
  <name xml:lang="ur_PK">ایکسفس توانائی منیجر</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Менеджер живлення Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">‫Xfce توك مەنبە باشقۇرغۇچ</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Xfce güç yönetimi</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">XFCE strömhanterare</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Управник напајања ИксФЦЕ-а</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Përgjegjës energjie Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Xfce upravljalnik porabe energije</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Správca napájania Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Диспетчер питания Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Administratorul de energie Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Gestor de energia do Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Gerenciador de energia do Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Menedżer zasilania Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Gestionari d'alimentacion Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Xfce-energiebeheer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Xfce-strømstyring</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Xfce maitinimo tvarkytuvė</name>
  <name xml:lang="lo">ຕົວຈັດການພະລັງງານ Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">xfce 전원 관리자</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Xfce-ის ენერგიის მმართველი</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Xfce 電源管理</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Gestore dell'energia di Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Xfce energiakezelő</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">מנהל צריכת חשמל Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Xestor de enerxía de Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Xfce:n virranhallinta</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Xfce energia-kudeatzailea</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Xfce vooluhaldur</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Gestor de energía de Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Xfce power manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_CA">Xfce power manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Διαχειριστής ρεύματος Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Xfce-Energieverwaltung</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Xfce Strømstyring</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Správce napájení pro Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Gestor d'energia del Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Управление на захранването на Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Xestor d'enerxía de Xfce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مدير طاقة Xfce</name>
  <summary>Manage and reduce power consumption of computer and devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">管理並減少電腦與裝置的電源消耗</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">管理和降低计算机和设备的功耗</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Quản lý và giảm mức tiêu thụ nguồn năng của máy tính và thiết bị</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Керуйте та зменшуйте енергоспоживання комп’ютера та пристроїв</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ug">كومپيۇتېر ۋە ئۈسكۈنىنىڭ توك سەرپىياتىنى باشقۇرىدۇ ۋە ئازايتىدۇ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Bilgisayar ve cihazların güç tüketimini yönetin ve azaltın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">จัดการและลดการใช้พลังงานของคอมพิวเตอร์และอุปกรณ์ต่าง ๆ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hantera och minska strömförbrukningen för datorer och enheter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Управља и смањује потрошњу снаге рачунара и уређаја</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Administroni dhe ulni konsum energjie të kompjuterit dhe pajisjeve</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljanje in zmanjševanje porabe energije računalnikov in naprav</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Spravovať a znížiť spotrebu energie počítača a zariadení</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Управление и снижение энергопотребления компьютера и устройств</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Gestionează și reduce consumul de energie al calculatorului și al dispozitivelor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gerir e reduzir o consumo de energia do computador e dos dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Administre e reduza o consumo de energia do computador e de dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie i zmniejszanie zużycia energii przez komputer i urządzenia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Gerir e reduire la consomacion energetica de l'ordenador e dels periferics</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Beheer en verminder stroomverbruik van computer en andere apparaten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Behandle og redusere strømforbruket til datamaskinen og dens enheter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Valdyti ir mažinti kompiuterio ir įrenginių energijos vartojimą</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lo">ຈັດການ ແລະ ຫຼຸດຜ່ອນການໃຊ້ພະລັງງານຂອງຄອມພິວເຕີ ແລະ ອຸປະກອນຕ່າງໆ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">컴퓨터와 장치의 전력 소비량을 관리하고 줄입니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Компьютер және құрылғылардың эл. қорегін тұтынуын басқару және азайту</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">მართეთ და შეამცირეთ ენერგიის ხარჯვა თქვენი კომპიუტერისთვის და მოწყობილობებისთვის</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">コンピューターとデバイスの消費電力を管理および削減する</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestisce e riduce il consumo della memoria del computer e dei dispositivi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Számítógépek és eszközök energiafogyasztásának kezelése és csökkentése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">נהל והפחת צריכת חשמל של מחשב והתקנים</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xestionar e reducir o consumo de enerxía do computador e dos dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gère et réduit la consommation d’énergie de l’ordinateur et des appareils</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ordenagailuen eta gailuen energia-kontsumoa kudeatu eta murriztu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Halda ja vähenda arvutite ning seadmete elektritarbimist</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Administra y reduce el consumo de energía del ordenador y dispositivos.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Manage and reduce power consumption of computer and devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_CA">Manage and reduce power consumption of computer and devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Διαχείρηση και μείωση της κατανάλωσης ενέργειας υπολογιστή και συσκευών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Verwalten und reduzieren des Stromverbrauchs von Rechner und Geräten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Håndter og reducer strømforbruget for computeren og enhederne</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Spravujte a snižujte spotřebu energie počítače a zařízení</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestiona i redueix el consum d'energia de l'ordinador i els dispostitius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Управляване и редуциране консумацията на енергия на компютъра и устройствата</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Xestiona ya amenorga el consumu d'enerxía en ordenadores ya preseos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">إدارة وتقليل إستهلاك الحاسوب والأجهزة للطاقة</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Xfce power manager manages the power sources on the computer
    and the devices that can be controlled to reduce their power
    consumption (such as LCD brightness level, monitor sleep,
    CPU frequency scaling).
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Xfce 電源管理員管理在您的電腦及裝置上的電力來源，可以減少電力消耗(像是液晶螢幕的亮度、顯示器睡眠、CPU時脈調整等)。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Xfce 电源管理器管理计算机的电源以及能够控制并降低功耗的设备（例如液晶显示器亮度级别，显示器睡眠，CPU频率等等）。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Trình quản lý nguồn Xfce quản lý các nguồn nguồn trên máy tính và thiết bị có thể được điều khiển để giảm mức tiêu thụ nguồn năng của chúng (chẳng hạn như mức độ sáng LCD, chế độ ngủ của màn hình, thang đo tần số CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Менеджер живлення Xfce керує джерелами живлення комп’ютера і пристроями, які можна контролювати, зменшуючи споживання енергії ними (такі, як рівень яскравості LCD, монітор сплячки, шкалювання частотою процесора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ug">توك مەنبە باشقۇرغۇچ كومپيۇتېرنىڭ توك مەنبەسى ۋە ئېنېرگىيە تېجىگىلى ۋە باشقۇرغىلى بولىدىغان ئۈسكۈنە (مەسىلەن، سۇيۇق كىرىستال كۆرسەتكۈچ يەنى LCD نىڭ يورۇقلۇق دەرىجىسى، كۆزەتكۈچنى ئۇخلىتىش، CPU چاستوتى قاتارلىق) نى باشقۇرىدۇ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tt">Xfce туендыру менеджеры, энергия куллануны киметү өчен, мондый мөмкинлеге булган компьютер һәм җайланмаларның туену чыганаклары белән идарә итә (мәсәлән, экран яртыртылышы яктылыгы, мониторның көтү режимы, процессор ешлыгын үзгәртү).</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Xfce güç yöneticisi, bilgisayardaki güç kaynaklarını ve güç tüketimlerini azaltmak için denetlenebilen aygıtları (LCD parlaklık düzeyi, ekran uyku kipi, MİB frekans ölçekleme gibi) yönetir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce จะจัดการแหล่งพลังงานของคอมพิวเตอร์และอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ ที่สามารถควบคุมได้ เพื่อลดการใช้พลังงานของอุปกรณ์เหล่านั้น (เช่น ระดับความสว่างของ LCD, การหลับของจอภาพ, การปรับความถี่ซีพียู)</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Xfce strömhanterare handhar datorns kraftkällor och enheterna som kan kontrolleras för att reducera deras konsumtion av ström (som till exempel LCD-ljusnivå, skärmsömn, CPU-frekvensskalning).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник напајања Иксфце-а управља потрошачима на рачунару и уређајима којима може да се управља ради штедње (као што су ступањ осветљења ЛЦД-а, успављивање заслона, подешавање учесталости процесора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Përgjegjësi Xfce i energjisë administron burime energjie te kompjuteri dhe pajisjet që mund të kontrollohet, për të zvogëluar konsumin e energjisë prej tyre (të tilla si shkallë ndriçimi LCD, fjetje ekrani, përshkallëzim frekuencash CPU-je).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik porabe energije Xfce upravlja z viri energije na računalniku in napravami, ki jih lahko nadzoruje za zmanjšanje porabe energije (knp. svetlost LCD zaslonov, mirovanje zaslonov, nadzorovanje hitrosti procesorja).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Správca napájania Xfce  spravuje zdroje napájania počítača a zariadenia, ktorým možno riadiť potrebu napájania (napr. úroveň jasu LCD, uspanie monitora, nastavenie frekvencie CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Диспетчер питания Xfce управляет источниками питания компьютера и устройств, которые имеют такую возможность, для снижения энергопотребления (например, яркость подсветки экрана, ждущий решим монитора, изменение частоты процессора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Administratorul de energie Xfce gestionează sursele de alimentare ale sistemului și dispozitivele ce pot fi controlate pentru a reduce consumul de energie, de exemplu prin reducerea luminozității ecranelor LCD, ori trecerea lor în repaus, scalarea frecvenței procesoarelor etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O gestor de energia do Xfce faz a gestão das fontes de energia no computador e nos dispositivos que possam ser controlados, para reduzir o consumo de energia (nível de luminosidade do LCD, suspensão do monitor, escalonamento da frequência da CPU, etc).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O gerenciador de energia do Xfce gerencia as fontes de energia no computador e os dispositivos que podem ser controlados para reduzir o seu consumo de energia (como o nível de brilho do LCD, monitorar suspensão, escalonamento da frequência do CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Menedżer zasilania Xfce odpowiada za zarządzanie poborem energii przez komputer oraz urządzenia do niego podłączone (np. dopasowując jasność ekranu, usypiając monitor, przeskalowując taktowanie CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Lo gestionari d’alimentacion gerís las sorgas d’energia sus l’ordenador e los periferics que se pòt contrarotlar per reduire lor consomacion energetica (coma lo nivèl de luminositat LCD, la velha del monitor, la mesa a l’escala de la frequéncia CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Xfce Energiebeheerder beheert de krachtbronnen op de computer en de apparaten waarvan het stroomverbruik kan worden teruggebracht (zoals schermhelderheid, slaapstand van beeldscherm, verlagen van CPU-frequentie).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Xfce-strømstyringen tar hånd om strømkildene på maskinen og enhetene som kan kontrolleres for å redusere deres strømforbruk (som lysnivå på LCD-skjerm, søvn for monitor, og justering av prosessorfrekvens).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Pengurus kuasa Xfce mengurus sumber kuasa pada komputer dan peranti yang dapat dikawal untuk mengurangkan penggunaan kuasa mereka (seperti aras kecerahan LCD, mod tidur monitor, penskalaan frekuensi CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Xfce maitinimo tvarkytuvė kompiuteryje valdo maitinimo šaltinius bei įrenginius, kurie gali būti valdomi, siekiant sumažinti jų energijos vartojimą (tokius kaip LCD ryškumo lygį, monitoriaus užmigdymą, procesoriaus dažnio keitimą).</p>
    <p xml:lang="lo">ຕົວຈັດການພະລັງງານ Xfce ຈັດການແຫຼ່ງພະລັງງານໃນຄອມພິວເຕີ ແລະ ອຸປະກອນທີ່ສາມາດຄວບຄຸມເພື່ອຫຼຸດການໃຊ້ພະລັງງານໄດ້ (ເຊັ່ນ ລະດັບຄວາມສະຫວ່າງ LCD, ການພັກຈໍພາບ, ການປັບຄວາມຖີ່ CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Xfce 전원 관리자는 컴퓨터와 전력 소모 감소를 제어(LCD 밝기, 모니터 대기 상태, CPU 주파수 조정)할 수 있는 장치에 붙은 전원을 관리합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">Xfce ಪವರ್ ಮ್ಯಾನೇಜರ್ ಕಂಪ್ಯೂಟರ್ನಲ್ಲಿ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಮೂಲಗಳನ್ನು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಅವುಗಳ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಬಳಕೆಯನ್ನು ಕಡಿಮೆ ಮಾಡಲು ನಿಯಂತ್ರಿಸಬಹುದಾದ ಸಾಧನಗಳನ್ನು (ಉದಾಹರಣೆಗೆ ಎಲ್ಸಿಡಿ ಪ್ರಕಾಶಮಾನ ಮಟ್ಟ, ಮಾನಿಟರ್ ನಿದ್ರೆ, ಸಿಪಿಯು ಆವರ್ತನ ಸ್ಕೇಲಿಂಗ್).</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы компьютердің эл. қорек көздерін және қоректі тұтынуды баптауға болатын құрылғыларды (LCD экран жарықтылығы, мониторды ұйықтату, процессор жиілігін өзгерту сияқты) басқарады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Xfce-ის ენერგიის მმართველი მართავს ენერგიის წყაროებს კომპიუტერისთვის და მოწყობილობებისთვის, რომლებიც შეგიძლიათ მართოთ ისე, რომ მათი ენერგიის ხარჯი შეამციროთ (მაგ: LCD ეკრანის სიკაშკაშე, ძილი, CPU-ის სიხშირის მართვა და ა.შ.).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Xfce 電源管理はコンピューターおよび消費電力を制御可能なデバイス (LCD の輝度レベル、モニターのスリープ、CPU の動作周波数など) の電源を管理します。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il gestore dell'energia di Xfce serve a controllare le fonti di energia del computer e dei dispositivi che possono essere regolate per ridurre il loro consumo (come la luminosità dello schermo, lo spegnimento del monitor o la frequenza della CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Xfce-orkustýringin stjórnar afluppsprettum á tölvunni og þeim tækjum þar sem hægt er að stjórna orkunýtingu (svo sem birtustigi LCD-skjás, skjásvæfingu, tíðnikvörðun CPU-örgjörva, o.þ.h.).</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Manajer daya Xfce mengelola sumber daya pada komputer untuk mengurangi konsumsi daya (seperti kecerahan layar, penonaktifan tampilan, penyesuaian frekuensi CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="hye">Xfce լիցքի կառավարիչը կառավարում է այն համակարգիչների եւ սարքերի հոսանքի աղբիւրները, որոնց hոսանքի սպառումը հնարաւոր է նուազեցնել (աւրինակ՝ հեղուկաբիւրեղային ցուցասարքի պայծառութեան մակարդակը, ցուցասարքի հանգիստի եղանակը, ԿՄՍ֊ի հաճախութեան չափումը):</p>
    <p xml:lang="hy_AM">Xfce լիցքի կառավարիչը կառավարում է այն համակարգիչների եւ սարքերի հոսանքի աղբիւրները, որոնց hոսանքի սպառումը հնարաւոր է նուազեցնել (աւրինակ՝ հեղուկաբիւրեղային ցուցասարքի պայծառութեան մակարդակը, ցուցասարքի հանգիստի եղանակը, ԿՄՍ֊ի հաճախութեան չափում):</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Xfce energiakezelő kezeli a számítógép energiaforrásait, és azokat az eszközöket, amelyek vezérlésével csökkenthető az energiafogyasztás (mint az LCD fényereje, a kijelző alvása, a CPU frekvenciaskálázása).</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Xfce upravitelj energijom upravlja izvorima energije računala i uređajima kojima se može smanjiti razina potrošnje energije (kao što su razina svjetline LCD zaslona, spavanje monitora, promijena frekvencije CPU-a).</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מנהל צריכת חשמל Xfce מנהל את מקורות החשמל של המחשב וההתקנים אשר נתונים לבקרה כדי להפחית את צריכת החשמל שלהם (כגון רמת בהירות מסך LCD, שינת תצוגה, שינוי תדירות CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O xestor de enerxía do Xfce encárgase das fontes de enerxía do computador e os dispositivos que poden ser controlados para reducir o consumo de enerxía (como o nivel de brillo da pantalla, a suspensión da pantalla e a graduación de frecuencia do procesador.)</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce gère les sources d’alimentation sur l’ordinateur et les périphériques qui peuvent être contrôlés afin de réduire leur consommation d’énergie (tel que le niveau de luminosité de l’écran LCD, la mise en veille du moniteur, l’échelonnement de la fréquence du CPU). </p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Xfce:n virranhallinta hallitsee tietokoneen virtalähteitä ja laitteita, joiden virrankäyttöä voidaan vähentää (esimerkiksi näytön kirkkauden taso ja lepotila, prosessorin tehon säätö).</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Xfce energia kudeatzaileak ordenagailuko elikatze-iturriak eta energia-kontsumoa murrizteko kontrola daitezkeen gailuak (adibidez, LCD distira-maila, loa kontrolatzea, PUZ maiztasun-eskalatzea) kudeatzen ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Xfce vooluhaldur haldab arvuti toiteallikaid ning erinevate seadmete voolutarvet (näiteks LCD ekraani eredus, monitori väljalülitamine ning protsessori taktsageduse automaatne muutmine).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El gestor de energía de Xfce gestiona las fuentes de energía del equipo y los dispositivos que se pueden controlar para reducir su consumo de energía (como el nivel de brillo de la pantalla, el ahorro de energía del monitor o el escalado de la la frecuencia del procesador).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Xfce power manager manages the power sources on the computer and the devices that can be controlled to reduce their power consumption (such as LCD brightness level, monitor sleep, CPU frequency scaling).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_CA">Xfce power manager manages the power sources on the computer and the devices that can be controlled to reduce their power consumption (such as LCD brightness level, monitor sleep, CPU frequency scaling).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">Xfce power manager manages the power sources on the computer and the devices that can be controlled to reduce their power consumption (such as LCD brightness level, monitor sleep, CPU frequency scaling).</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο διαχειριστής ρεύματος του xfce διαχειρίζεται την ενέργεια στον υπολογιστή και στις συσκευές που μπορούν να ελεγχθούν, για να μειωθεί η κατανάλωση ενέργειας (όπως το επίπεδο φωτεινότητας σε οθόνες LCD, την αναμονή και τη ρύθμιση συχνότητας του επεξεργαστή).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Xfce-Energieverwaltung verwaltet die Energiequellen des Rechners und die Geräte, die gesteuert werden können, um ihren Energieverbrauch zu reduzieren (wie zum Beispiel LCD-Helligkeit, Stromsparmodus des Bildschirms, CPU-Frequenzskalierung).</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Xfce Strømstyring håndterer strømkilderne på computeren og de enheder, der kan styres til at reducere deres strømforbrug (såsom lysstyrken på LCD-skærme, hvile og skalering af CPU-frekvens).</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Správce napájení pro Xfce spravuje zdroje napájení počítače a zařízení, která lze ovládat, za účelem snížení spotřeby energie (např. úroveň jasu LCD displeje, uspání monitoru, nastavení frekvence procesoru).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El gestor d'energia de Xfce gestiona les fonts d'energia de l'ordinador i els dispositius que es poden controlar per reduir-ne el consum energètic (com ara el nivell de brillantor del LCD, el repòs del monitor i l'escalat de freqüència de la CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Xfce power manager управлява източници на захранване на компютъра и устройствата, които могат да бъдат контролирани, за да се намали потреблението на енергия (като ниво на яркост на LCD, монитор, сън, честотата на процесора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Кіраўнік сілкавання xfce кіруе крыніцамі сілкавання камп’ютара і падлучаных прылад, якімі можна кіраваць для памяншэння выкарыстання энергіі (напрыклад яркасць экрана, рэжым сну манітора, змена чашчыні працэсара).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">El xestor d'enerxía Xfce xestiona les fontes d'enerxía del ordenador ya los preseos, amenorgando el so consumu d'enerxía (Rellumu de pantalles LCD, apagáu de monitor, escaláu de frecuencia de CPU...)</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">مدير الطاقة اكسفس يدير مصادر الطاقة على الحاسوب والأجهزة التي يتحكم فيها للحد من استهلاك الطاقة (مثل مستوى سطوع الشاشة، نوم العارض، تحجيم تردد المعالج).</p>
    <p>In addition, Xfce power manager provides a set of freedesktop-compliant
    DBus interfaces to inform other applications about current power level
    so that they can adjust their power consumption, and it provides the inhibit
    interface which allows applications to prevent automatic sleep actions
    via the power manager; as an example, the operating system’s package manager
    should make use of this interface while it is performing update operations.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">另外，Xfce 電源管理員提供了一組相容於 freedesktop 的 DBus 介面，以通知其他應用程式目前的電力狀態，這樣它們就可以調整電力消耗，它也提供了抑制介面，讓應用程式可以避免電源管理員自動進入睡眠；例如，作業系統的軟體包管理員需要在它執行升級動作時使用這個介面。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">与此同时，Xfce 电源管理器提供了一组符合 freedesktop.org 规范的 DBus 接口，用于通知其他应用程序以当前的电量级别，让它们调整电量使用，同时提供用于阻止电源管理器睡眠动作的接口；软件更新管理器应该使用此接口来保障更新操作顺利完成。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Ngoài ra, trình quản lý nguồn Xfce còn cung cấp một bộ giao diện DBus tương thích với freedesktop để thông báo cho các ứng dụng khác giới thiệu mức nguồn hiện tại để chúng có thể điều chỉnh mức tiêu thụ nguồn năng của mình và nó cung cấp giao diện ức chế cho phép các ứng dụng ngăn chặn các hành động ngủ tự động thông qua trình quản lý nguồn; ví dụ: trình quản lý gói của hệ điều hành nên sử dụng giao diện này trong khi thực hiện các hoạt động cập nhật.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">На додаток, менеджер живлення Xfce впроваджує інтерфейси DBus, сумісні з правилами freedesktop, для інформування користувачів про поточний рівень заряду, завдяки чому користувачі можуть регулювати споживання енергії, а також інтерфейс гамування, який дозволяє користувачам  запобігати автоматичному засинанню через менеджер живлення; наприклад, менеджер пакунків операційної системи повинен використовувати цей інтерфейс поки іде оновлення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ug">ئۇنىڭدىن باشقا، Xfce توك مەنبە باشقۇرغۇچ بىر يۈرۈش freedesktop.org نىڭ ئۆلچىمىدىكى DBus ئارايۈزى تەمىنلىگەن بولۇپ، باشقا پىروگراممىلارغا نۆۋەتتىكى توك دەرىجىسىنى ئۇقتۇرۇپ، توك ئىشلىتىش مىقدارىنى تەڭشەش شۇنداقلا توك مەنبە باشقۇرغۇچنىڭ ئۇخلاش ھالىتىگە كىرىشنىڭ ئالدىنى ئېلىش ئارايۈزى بىلەن تەمىنلەيدۇ؛ مەسىلەن، مەشغۇلات سىستېمىسىدىكى يۇمشاق دېتال يېڭىلاشنى باشقۇرغۇچ مەزكۇر ئارايۈزنى ئىشلىتىپ يېڭىلاش مەشغۇلاتىنىڭ ئوڭۇشلۇق تاماملىنىشىغا كاپالەتلىك قىلىدۇ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tt">Өстәмә рәвештә, Xfce туендыру менеджеры, үзләренең энергия куллануын үзгәртә алсынга хәзерге корылу дәрәҗәсе турында башка кушымталарга хәбәр итү өчен, freedesktop белән ярашлы DBus интерфейслар җыелмасын тәкъдим итә. Шулай ук, кушымталарга туендыру менеджерында көтү режимы өчен автоматик гамәлләрне тыярга мөмкинлек бирә торган интерфейс та бар, мәсәлән, операцион система пакетлары менеджеры яңарту буенча гамәлләр башкарганда әлеге интерфейсны кулланырга тиеш.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Xfce güç yöneticisi, ek olarak, şu anki güç düzeyiyle ilgili diğer uygulamaları bilgilendirerek güç tüketimlerini ayarlamak için freedesktop uyumlu DBus arayüz takımı ve güç yöneticisi aracılığıyla uygulamaların, kendiliğinden uyku eylemlerini önlemelerini sağlayan engelleyici arayüzü sağlar. Örneğin, işletim sisteminin paket yöneticisi, güncelleme işlemlerini gerçekleştirirken bu arayüzü kullanabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">นอกจากนี้ ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce ยังจัดเตรียมอินเทอร์เฟซ DBus ตามข้อกำหนดของ freedesktop เพื่อแจ้งอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ เกี่ยวกับระดับพลังงานปัจจุบัน เพื่อให้อุปกรณ์เหล่านั้นปรับการใช้พลังงานของตน และยังจัดเตรียมอินเทอร์เฟซสำหรับการระงับ ซึ่งทำให้โปรแกรมต่างๆ สามารถป้องกันการหลับอัตโนมัติผ่านระบบจัดการพลังงานได้ ตัวอย่างเช่น โปรแกรมจัดการแพกเกจของระบบปฏิบัติการควรใช้อินเทอร์เฟซดังกล่าวขณะดำเนินการอัปเดตระบบ</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Utöver det, tillhandahåller Xfce-strömhanteraren en uppsättning freedesktop-compliant DBus-gränssnitt för att informera andra program om aktuell energinivå så att de kan justera sin energikonsumtion, och den tillhandahåller spärrgränssnitt som tillåter program att förhindra automatiska vilolägesåtgärder via energisparhanteraren; som ett exempel, bör operativsystemets pakethanterare utnyttja detta gränssnitt medan det utför uppdateringsoperationer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник напајања ИксФЦЕ-а има додатке сагласне са сучељима Д-сабирнице ради обавештавања других програма о тренутном ступњу напајања да би они смањили своју потрошњу, и омогућава сучеље које другим програмима омогућава да спрече радње самосталног успављивања преко управника напајања; на пример, управник пакета система би требао да користи ово сучеље при извршавању радњи надградње.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Veç kësaj, përgjegjësi Xfce i energjisë furnizon një grup ndërfaqesh DBus të përputhshme me freedesktop-in për të informuar aplikacione të tjera mbi nivele energjie, që kështu ato të mund të ujdisin konsumin e energjisë nga ana e tyre, dhe furnizon ndërfaqen e pengimeve e cila u lejon aplikacioneve të parandalojnë veprime kalimi automatik në fjetje përmes përgjegjësi të energjisë; si një shembull, përgjegjësi i paketave të sistemit operativ do të duhej të shfrytëzonte këtë ndërfaqe, teksa është duke kryer veprime përditësimi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Poleg tega Xfce upravljalnik porabe energije ponuja nabor freedesktop ustreznih DBus vmesnikov, ki druge aplikacije obveščajo o trenutnem stanu nivojev energije, tako da lahko te prilagodijo svojo porabo. Poleg tega ponuja vmesnik za onemogočanje, ki dovoljuje programom, da preprečijo samodejno spanje preko upravljalnika porabe energije. Primer za to je sistemski program za namestitev paketov, ki bi moral uporabljati ta vmesnik, ko izvaja posodobitve.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Ďalej, Správca napájania Xfce poskytuje sadu rozhraní DBus zhodných s freedesktop na informovanie iných aplikácií o aktuálnej úrovni napájania, aby mohli prispôsobiť svoju spotrebu a poskytuje blokovacie rozhranie, ktoré umožňuje aplikáciám zablokovať akcie automatického uspania pomocou správcu napájania; ako príklad: správca balíkov operačného systému môže použiť toto rozhranie počas aktualizácie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Дополнительно, диспетчер питания Xfce предоставляет набор интерфейсов DBus, совместимых с freedesktop, для оповещения других приложений о текущем уровне заряда, чтобы они могли изменить своё потребление энергии. Также имеется интерфейс, позволяющий приложениям запретить автоматические действия для ждущего режима в менеджере питания, например, менеджер пакетов операционной системы должен использовать данный интерфейс при выполнении действий по обновлению.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">În plus, administratorul de energie Xfce oferă un set de interfețe DBus ce respectă standardele freedesktop.org pentru a informa alte programe despre nivelul bateriei, astfel încât acestea să-și ajusteze consumul de energie. Mai mult, oferă o interfață de prevenire a trecerii automate în repaus pentru programele ce necesită continuarea funcționării pentru o perioadă de timp, de exemplu un gestionar de pachete ce actualizează sistemul.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Adicionalmente, o gestor de energia do Xfce providencia um conjunto de interfaces DBus do projeto 'freedesktop' (que transmitem a informação do nível de energia a outras aplicações para que elas possam ajustar o seu consumo) e a interface de inibição que permite às aplicações impedirem as ações automáticas de suspensão via gestor de energia (por exemplo, o gestor de pacotes do sistema deverá utilizar esta interface enquanto estiver a efetuar operações de atualização).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Além disso, o gerenciador de energia do Xfce fornece um conjunto de interfaces DBus compatíveis com o freedesktop para informar outros aplicativos sobre o nível de energia atual, para que possam ajustar seu consumo de energia, e fornece a interface de inibição, que permite que os aplicativos evitem ações automáticas de suspensão através do gerenciador de energia; por exemplo, o gerenciador de pacotes do sistema operacional deve fazer uso dessa interface, enquanto ele estiver executando operações de atualização.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ponadto menedżer zasilania Xfce zapewnia zestaw interfejsów DBus zgodnych ze standardem freedesktop, które informują inne programy o bieżącym poziomie zasilania, aby mogły dostosować swoje zużycie energii, oraz zapewnia interfejs wstrzymywania, który umożliwia programom zapobieganie automatycznym czynnościom uśpienia za pośrednictwem menedżera zasilania; na przykład menedżer pakietów systemu operacyjnego powinien korzystać z tego interfejsu podczas wykonywania operacji aktualizacji.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">De mai, lo gestionari d’alimentacion provesís un jòc d’interfàcias compatiblas amb DBus per assabentar las autras aplicacions a prepaus lo nivèl actuala d’energia per que pòsca ajustar la consomacion energetica, fornís l’interfàcia d’inibicion que permet a las aplicacions d’evitar las accions de mesa en velha automatica ; per exemple, lo gestionari de paquets del sistèma operatiu deu se servir d’aquesta interfàcia pendent l’execucion de las operacions de mesa a jorn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bovendien levert Xfce Energiebeheerder een stel DBus-bedieningsschillen die voldoen aan de freedesktop-standaard, om andere toepassingen in te lichten omtrent het huidige energieniveau, zodat zij hun energieverbruik kunnen bijstellen. Ook levert hij aan toepassingen de bedieningsschil om automatische slaapstand via Energiebeheerder te voorkomen. Bijvoorbeeld: de pakketbeheerder van het besturingssysteem zou deze bedieningsschil moeten gebruiken wanneer hij programma's aan het bijwerken is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">I tillegg har Xfce-strømstyring et knippe freedesktop-støttede DBus-grensesnitt for å informere programmer om gjeldende strømnivå så de kan regulere sine strømforbruk. Grensesnittet tillater også programmer å midlertidig hindre dvalgang. Som et eksempel bruker pakkebehandleren dette grensesnittet når den utfører oppdateringer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Tambahan pula, pengurus kuasa Xfce menyediakan satu set antaramuka DBus menuruti-freedesktop untuk memaklumkan aplikasi lain mengenai aras kuasa semasa supaya ia dapat melaras penggunaan kuasa mereka, dan ia menyediakan juga antaramuka rencat yang membolehkan aplikasi menghalang tindakan tidur automatik melalui pengurus kuasa; contohnya, pengurus pakej sistem pengoperasian menggunakan antaramuka ini ketika ia membuat kemaskini operasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Be to, Xfce maitinimo tvarkytuvė parūpina su freedesktop suderinamą DBus sąsajų rinkinį, skirtą informuoti kitas programas apie esamą energijos lygį, suteikiantį programoms galimybę reguliuoti savo energijos vartojimą ir draudimo sąsają, leidžiančią programoms, per maitinimo tvarkytuvę neleisti užmigdymo veiksmų; pavyzdžiui, sistemos paketų tvarkytuvė, atlikdama atnaujinimo operacijas, turėtų pasinaudoti šia sąsaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lo">ນອກຈາກນັ້ນ, ຕົວຈັດການພະລັງງານ Xfce ຍັງໃຫ້ບໍລິການ DBus interface ຕາມມາດຕະຖານ freedesktop ເພື່ອແຈ້ງແອັບອື່ນໆກ່ຽວກັບລະດັບພະລັງງານປັດຈຸບັນ ເພື່ອໃຫ້ພວກເຂົາປັບການໃຊ້ພະລັງງານໄດ້, ແລະ ຍັງມີ interface ສຳລັບຢັບຢັ້ງ (inhibit) ເພື່ອໃຫ້ແອັບປ້ອງກັນການພັກເຄື່ອງອັດຕະໂນມັດໄດ້; ຕົວຢ່າງເຊັ່ນ ຕົວຈັດການແພັກເກດຂອງລະບົບຄວນໃຊ້ interface ນີ້ໃນຂະນະທີ່ກຳລັງອັບເດດລະບົບ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">게다가, Xfce 전원 관리자에서는 현재 전원 상태를 다른 프로그램에 제공하는 freedesktop 호환 DBus 인터페이스를 제공하여 전력 소모를 줄일 수 있고, 전원 관리자가 자동으로 대기상태로 진입하는 동작을 다른 프로그램이 막을 수 있게 하는 억제 인터페이스를 제공합니다. 예를 들자면 운영체제 꾸러미 관리자에서는 업데이트 동작을 수행하는 동안 이 인터페이스를 활용합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">ಇದರ ಜೊತೆಗೆ, Xfce ಪವರ್ ಮ್ಯಾನೇಜರ್ ಪ್ರಸ್ತುತ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಶಕ್ತಿಯ ಮಟ್ಟದಲ್ಲಿ ಇತರ ಅನ್ವಯಿಕೆಗಳನ್ನು ತಿಳಿಸಲು ಡೆಸ್ಕ್ಟಾಪ್-ಕಂಪ್ಲೈಂಟ್ DBus ಇಂಟರ್ಫೇಸ್ಗಳ ಒಂದು ಸೆಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದರಿಂದಾಗಿ ಅವುಗಳು ತಮ್ಮ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಬಳಕೆಯನ್ನು ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಮ್ಯಾನೇಜರ್ ಮೂಲಕ ಸ್ವಯಂಚಾಲಿತ ನಿದ್ರೆ ಕಾರ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ತಡೆಯಲು ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ಗಳನ್ನು ಅನುಮತಿಸುವ ಪ್ರತಿಬಂಧಕ ಇಂಟರ್ಫೇಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ; ಉದಾಹರಣೆಯಾಗಿ, ಆಪರೇಟಿಂಗ್ ಸಿಸ್ಟಮ್ನ ಪ್ಯಾಕೇಜ್ ಮ್ಯಾನೇಜರ್ ಈ ಇಂಟರ್ಫೇಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ನವೀಕರಣ ಕಾರ್ಯಾಚರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸುತ್ತಿರುವಾಗ ಬಳಸಬೇಕು.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Сонымен қатар, Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы басқа қолданбаларға ағымдағы эл. қорек деңгейі туралы ақпаратты ұсынуға арналған freedesktop-үйлесімді DBus интерфейстерін қамтамасыз етеді. Оның көмегімен қолданбалар өздерінің қоректі тұтыну деңгейлерін баптап, ұйықтатуға жол бермеу мүмкіндігін пайдалана алады. Мысалы, жүйені жаңартатын дестелер басқарушысы өз жұмысын сәтті аяқтау үшін оны қолдана алады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">დამატებით, Xfce-ის ენერგიის მმართველი მოგაწოდებთ freedesktop-თან თავსებად DBus-ის ინტერფეისს, რომ უთხრათ აპლიკაციებს მიმდინარე ენერგიის დონის შესახებ, რომ მათ თავიანთი ენერგიის ხარჯვა მართონ და ასევე აქვს ინტერფეისი, რომელიც აპლიკაციებს საშუალებას აძლევს გამორთონ ავტომატური ძილი ან გამორთვა. მაგალითად, ეს ინტერფეისი უნდა გამოიყენოს პაკეტების მმართველმა, როცა ის სისტემის განახლებითაა დაკავებული.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">さらに、Xfce 電源管理はほかのアプリケーションに現在の電源レベルなどを提供するための freedesktop.org 準拠の DBus インターフェイスも用意しています。これを利用してアプリケーションから消費電力の調整が行えます。ほかに、電源制御が自動で行うスリープの一時的な抑止もできます。例えば、オペレーティングシステムのパッケージ管理がアップデート処理を行っている間などにこの機能を使用するといいでしょう。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Inoltre, il gestore dell'energia di Xfce fornisce una serie di interfacce DBus compatibili con freedesktop, utili a passare alle altre applicazioni informazioni sul livello energetico del sistema così da permettere loro di regolarsi in base ad esso. Fornisce anche un'interfaccia che consente alle applicazioni di impedire l'addormentamento automatico del sistema attraverso il gestore dell'energia; ad esempio, il gestore dei pacchetti del sistema dovrebbe utilizzare questa interfaccia durante gli aggiornamenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Selain itu, manajer daya Xfce juga menyediakan sekumpulan antar muka DBus yang kompatibel dengan freedesktop, yang dapat dipakai untuk mendapatkan informasi tentang tingkat daya tersisa dan mencegah sistem masuk pada mode tidur (saat diperlukan).</p>
    <p xml:lang="hye">Յաւելեալ․ Xfce լիցքի կառավարիչն ապահովում է DBus freedesktop համապատասխան միջավայրեր այլ ծրագրերի՝ լիցքի ներկայիս մակարդակի մասին տեղեկացնելու համար, որպէսզի նրանք կարգաւորեն մարտկոցի սպառումը, բացի դրանից մատակարարում է նաեւ միջավայր, որը թոյլ է տալիս ծրագրերին արգելել հանգստի ինքնաշխատ գործողութիւնները, լարման կառավարչի աւգնութեամբ․ աւրինակ՝ ԱՒՀ֊ի փաթեթների կառավարիչը պէտք է գործածի այս միջավայրը, թարմացումների ժամանակ։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hy_AM">Յաւելեալ․ Xfce լիցքի կառավարիչն ապահովում է DBus freedesktop համապատասխան միջավայրեր այլ ծրագրերի՝ լիցքի ներկայիս մակարդակի մասին տեղեկացնելու համար, որպէսզի նրանք կարգաւորեն մարտկոցի սպառումը, բացի դրանից մատակարարում է նաեւ միջավայր, որը թոյլ է տալիս ծրագրերին արգելել հանգստի ինքնաշխատ գործողութիւնները, լարման կառավարչի աւգնութեամբ․ աւրինակ՝ ԱՒՀ֊ի փաթեթների կառավարիչը պէտք է գործածի այս միջավայրը, թարմացումների ժամանակ։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Továbbá az Xfce energiakezelő egy freedesktop-kompatibilis DBus interfészcsomagot biztosít, hogy értesítse a többi alkalmazást a jelenlegi energiaszintről, így azok is módosíthatják az energiafogyasztásukat, valamint biztosít egy megakadályozó interfészt is, amellyel megakadályozhatók az energiakezelő automatikus alvási műveletei. Például az operációs rendszer csomagkezelőjének célszerű használnia az interfészt a frissítési műveletek közben.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Uz to, Xfce upravitelj energijom pruža set DBus sučelja usklađenih s freedesktop standardom radi obaviještavanja drugih aplikacija o trenutnom stanju energije kako bi mogle prilagoditi svoju razinu potrošnje. Pruža i sučelje koje omogućava aplikacijama da zaustave automatsko spavanje sustava, npr. dok upravitelj programskim paketima ažurira sustav.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">בנוסף, מנהל צריכת חשמל Xfce מספק ערכה של ממשקי DBus תומכי freedesktop כדי ליידע יישומים אחרים על צריכת חשמל נוכחית על מנת שאלו יוכלו להתאים את צריכת החשמל שלהם, וכמו כן זו מספקת ממשק מניעה אשר מתיר ליישומים למנוע פעולות שינה אוטומטיות באמצעות מנהל צריכת החשמל; כדוגמה, מנהל החבילות של מערכת הפעלה צריך להשתמש בממשק זה בעת שזה מבצע פעולות עדכון.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ademais, o xestor de enerxía Xfce fornece un conxunto de interfaces DBus compatíbeis con freedesktop para informar a outras aplicacións sobre o nivel de potencia actual para que poidan axustar o seu consumo de enerxía e proporciona a interface de inhibición que permite que as aplicacións impidan as accións de suspensión automáticas a través do xestor de enerxía; como exemplo, o xestor de paquetes do sistema operativo, quen debería facer uso desta interface mentres está a realizar operacións de actualización.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">De plus, le gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce fournit un ensemble d’interfaces DBus conformes aux spécifications freedesktop pour informer les autres applications du niveau de charge actuel afin qu’elles puissent ajuster leur consommation d’énergie, et il fournit l’interface d’inhibition qui permet aux applications d’empêcher les actions automatiques de mise en veille via le gestionnaire d’alimentation ; par exemple, le gestionnaire de paquets du système d’exploitation devrait faire usage de cette interface pendant qu’il effectue ses opérations de mise à jour.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Lisäksi Xfce:n virranhallinta tarjoaa joitakin freedesktop-yhteensopivia DBus-rajapintoja ilmoittaakseen muille sovelluksille virran tasosta jotta ne voivat säätää omaa virrankulustaan ja jotta automaattinen keskeytys- ja lepotilaan siirtyminen voidaan välttää; esimerkiksi järjestelmän pakettienhallinnan tulisi käyttää tätä rajapintaa suorittaessaan päivitystoimintoja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Gainera, Xfce energia kudeatzaileak freedesktop-ekin bateragarriak diren DBus interfaze-multzo bat eskaintzen du, beste aplikazio batzuei egungo potentzia-mailaren berri emateko, haien energia-kontsumoa doitu ahal izan dezaten, eta aplikazioei energia kudeatzailearen bidez lo-ekintza automatikoak saihesteko aukera ematen dien inhibizio-interfazea ematen die; adibidez, sistema eragileko pakete-kudeatzaileak interfaze hori erabili behar du eguneratze-eragiketak egiten ari den bitartean.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Lisaks pakub Xfce vooluhaldur teistele rakendustele freedesktop-spetsifikatsiooni järgset DBus liidest, mille abil nad  saavad oma voolutarvet kohendada või blokeerida arvuti jäämise unne. Näiteks operatsioonisüsteemi paketihaldur võib kasutada viimatinimetatud funktsionaalsust süsteemi uuendamise ajal.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Además, el gestor de energía de Xfce proporciona un conjunto de interfaces D-Bus que cumplen las especificaciones de freedesktop.org para informar a otras aplicaciones de los niveles energía, de modo que puedan ajustar su consumo, y proporciona una interfaz de inhibición que permite a las aplicaciones impedir que se ejecuten acciones automáticas de ahorro de energía; ejemplo, el gestor de paquetes del sistema debería usar esta interfaz al ejecutar operaciones de actualización.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">In addition, Xfce power manager provides a set of freedesktop-compliant DBus interfaces to inform other applications about current power level so that they can adjust their power consumption, and it provides the inhibit interface which allows applications to prevent automatic sleep actions via the power manager; as an example, the operating system’s package manager should make use of this interface while it is performing update operations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_CA">In addition, Xfce power manager provides a set of freedesktop-compliant DBus interfaces to inform other applications about current power level so that they can adjust their power consumption, and it provides the inhibit interface which allows applications to prevent automatic sleep actions via the power manager; as an example, the operating system’s package manager should make use of this interface while it is performing update operations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">In addition, Xfce power manager provides a set of freedesktop-compliant DBus interfaces to inform other applications about current power level so that they can adjust their power consumption, and it provides the inhibit interface which allows applications to prevent automatic sleep actions via the power manager; as an example, the operating system’s package manager should make use of this interface while it is performing update operations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Επιπροσθέτως, ο διαχειριστής ρεύματος του Xfce παρέχει ένα σύνολο διεπαφών dbus, συμβατών με τα πρότυπα του freedesktop, για να ενημερώνει άλλες εφαρμογές για το τρέχον επίπεδο ενέργειας, ώστε να μπορούν να ρυθμίζουν την κατανάλωση ενέργειας και παρέχει επίσης διεπαφή παρεμπόδισης που επιτρέπει στις εφαρμογές να εμποδίζουν τις αυτόματες ενέργειες αναστολής του διαχειριστή ρεύματος. Για παράδειγμα, ο διαχειριστής πακέτων του λειτουργικού συστήματος πρέπει να κάνει χρήση αυτής της διεπαφής κατά την διάρκεια της λειτουργίας αναβάθμισης.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Zusätzlich stellt die Xfce-Energieverwaltung einen Satz an Freedesktop-konformen DBus-Schnittstellen zur Verfügung, um andere Anwendungen über den aktuellen Energiestand zu informieren, sodass diese ihren Energieverbrauch anpassen bzw. das automatische Versetzen in den Bereitschaftsmodus oder Ruhezustand verhindern können; beispielsweise sollte die Paketverwaltung des Betriebssystems diese Schnittstelle während der Aktualisierungsvorgänge benutzen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">I tillæg tilbyder Xfce Strømstyringen et sæt af freedesktop-kompatible DBus-grænseflader, der informerer andre programmer om det nuværende strømniveau, så de kan tilpasse deres strømforbrug, samtidig som det tilbyder inhibit-grænsefladen, der gør det muligt for programmer, at forhindre automatiske hvilehandlinger via strømstyring; som eksempel bør styresystemets pakkehåndtering gøre brug denne grænseflade, mens den udfører opdateringshandlinger.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Dále Správce napájení pro Xfce poskytuje sadu rozhraní sběrnice DBus v souladu s prvky freedesktop tak, že informuje ostatní aplikace o aktuální úrovni napájení, aby mohly přizpůsobit svoji spotřebu energie, a poskytuje aplikacím rozhraní pro předejití automatizovaných akcí pro přechod do režimu spánku. Toto rozhraní využívá například Správce balíčků systému při instalaci aktualizací.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">A més, el gestor d'energia de Xfce proporciona un conjunt d'interfícies DBus compatibles amb freedesktop per informar altres aplicacions del nivell d'energia perquè en puguin ajustar el consum i proporciona la interfície d'inhibició que permet a les aplicacions evitar accions automàtiques d'inactivitat a través del gestor d'energia; per exemple, l'administrador de paquets del sistema operatiu hauria de fer ús d'aquesta interfície mentre s'estiguin portant a terme les operacions d'actualització.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">В допълнение Xfce Power Manager предоставя набор от съвместими с freedesktop DBUS интерфейси за текущото ниво на мощност на други приложения, така че те да могат да нагодят собственото си потребление на енергия и осигурява възпрепятстващ интерфейс, който позволява на приложенията да предотвратяват автоматичното заспиване. Например, управлението на пакети би трябвало да използва възпрепятстващия интерфейс, докато извършва обновяване.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Дадаткова кіраўнік сілкавання Xfce вызначае інтэрфейсы для DBus, сумяшчальныя з freedesktop, для апавяшчэння праграм аб бягучым узроўні зараду батарэі, каб яны змянялі ўзровень спажывання энергіі. Таксама ёсць інтэрфейс, які прадухіляе аўтаматычны пераход у рэжым сну. Напрыклад, кіраўнік пакункаў мусіць выкарыстоўваць гэты інтэрфейс падчас абнаўлення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Amás, el xestor d'enerxía de Xfce proporciona delles interfaces Dbus compatibles con freedesktop, que dan-y a otros programes información tocante al nivel d'enerxía pa que puedan amenorgar el so consumu. Tamién proporciona interfaz de inhibición qu'impide que les aplicaciones faigan aiciones de suspensión automática via xestor d'enerxía. Por exemplu, el xestor de paquetes del sistema podría facer esto de mientres tea trabayando nos anovamientos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، يوفر مدير الطاقة اكسفس مجموعة من واجهات دبس المتوافقة فريدسكتوب لإبلاغ التطبيقات الأخرى بمستوى الطاقة الحالي بحيث يتمكنوا من ضبط استهلاك الطاقة، ويوفر واجهة مثبطة والتي تسمح للتطبيقات بمنع إجراءات النوم التلقائي عن طريق مدير الطاقة. على سبيل المثال، يجب أن يستخدم مدير حزمة نظام التشغيل هذه الواجهة أثناء تنفيذ عمليات التحديث.</p>
    <p>Xfce power manager also provides a plugin for the Xfce and LXDE panels
    to control LCD brightness levels and to monitor battery and device charge
    levels.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Xfce 電源管理員也為 Xfce 及 LXDE 面板提供了一個插件，用來控制液晶顯示器的亮度等級和監控電池及裝置的充電狀態。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Xfce 电源管理器还提供了一个用于 Xfce 和 LXDE 面板的插件，用于管理 LCD 亮度以及其他设备的电量级别。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Trình quản lý nguồn Xfce cũng cung cấp một plugin cho bảng Xfce và LXDE để kiểm soát mức độ sáng của màn hình LCD cũng như theo dõi mức sạc pin và thiết bị.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Менеджер живлення Xfce також пропонує додаток для панелей Xfce і LXDE для контролю рівня яскравості екрану і для контролю заряду акумулятора.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ug">Xfce توك مەنبە باشقۇرغۇچ يەنە Xfce ۋە LXDE كۆزنەكچە ئۈچۈن بىر قىستۇرما تەمىنلىگەن بولۇپ، سۇيۇق كىرىستال كۆرسەتكۈچ يەنى LCD نىڭ يورۇقلۇق دەرىجىسى ۋە باشقا ئۈسكۈنىدىكى توكداننى كۆزىتىش ۋە توكلىنىش دەرىجىسىنى باشقۇرۇشقا ئىشلىتىلىدۇ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tt">Xfce туендыру менеджеры шулай ук сыек кристаллы дисплейларның яктылыгын көйләү, батарея һәм җайланмаларның корылу дәрәҗәсен контрольдә тоту өчен Xfce һәм LXDE панельләре модулен тәкъдим итә.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Xfce güç yöneticisi; LCD parlaklığı düzeylerini, pil ve aygıt şarj düzeylerini izlemek için Xfce ve LXDE panel eklentilerini sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce ยังได้จัดเตรียมปลั๊กอินสำหรับพาเนล Xfce และ LXDE สำหรับปรับความสว่างของจอ LCD และเฝ้าสังเกตระดับประจุไฟของแบตเตอรี่และอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Xfce-strömhanteraren tillhandahåller också tillägg för Xfce- och LXDE-paneler för att kontrollera LCD-ljusstyrka och övervaka batteri och enheters laddningsnivåer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник напајања Иксфце-а такође има прикључак за полице Иксфце-а и Ликсде-а за управљање ступњем осветљења и надзором батерије и пуњења.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Përgjegjësi Xfce i energjisë furnizon gjithashtu një shtojcë për panele Xfce dhe LXDE që të kontrollohen shkallë ndriçimi LCD-je dhe të mbikëqyren shkallë ngarkimi të baterisë dhe pajisjes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Xfce upravljanik porabe energije ponuja tudi vtičnik za Xfce in LXDE panoje za upravljanje svetlobe LCD zaslonov in za nadzor nivojev baterije in naprave.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Správca napájania Xfce poskytuje aj zásuvný modul panela Xfce a LXDE na ovládanie úrovne jasu LCD a sledovanie úrovní batérie a nabíjacích zariadení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Диспетчер питания Xfce также предлагает модуль панелей Xfce и LXDE для изменения яркости ЖК-экранов и измерения уровня заряда батарей и устройств.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Administratorul de energie Xfce oferă un modul pentru panourile Xfce și LXDE pentru controlul luminozității LCD-urilor și pentru monitorizarea bateriei și a altor dispozitive ce necesită reîncărcare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O gestor de energia do Xfce também providencia um plugin de controlo da luminosidade do LCD e de visualização dos níveis de carga da bateria e dos dispositivos, para os painéis do Xfce e do LXDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O gerenciador de energia do Xfce também fornece um plug-in para os paineis do Xfce e LXDE para controlar os níveis de brilho do LCD e para monitorar os níveis de bateria e carga do dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Menedżer zasilania Xfce zapewnia wtyczkę dla paneli Xfce i LXDE, która umożliwia sterowanie poziomem jasności wyświetlacza LCD oraz monitorowanie poziomu naładowania akumulatora i urządzenia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Lo gestionari d’alimentacion Xfce provesís tanben un plugin pels panèls Xfce e LXDE per contrarotlar los nivèls de luminositat LCD, susvelhar la batariá del monitor e lo nivèl de carga de l’aparelh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Xfce-energiebeheerder levert ook een invoegsel voor de werkbalken van Xfce en LXDE, om de helderheid van LCD-schermen in te stellen en om de ladingsniveaus te bewaken van accu's en apparaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Xfce-strømstyring tilbys også som et tillegg for Xfce- og LXDE-paneler for å kontrollere LCD-lysstyrkenivå og gi oversikt over ladningsnivå til batteri og ladningsnivåer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Pengurus kuasa Xfce juga menyediakan satu pemalam panel Xfce dan LXDE untuk mengawal aras kecerahan LCD dan memantau aras pengecasan bateri dan peranti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Xfce maitinimo tvarkytuvė taip pat parūpina įskiepį, kuris skirtas Xfce ir LXDE skydeliams, ir kuris valdo LCD ryškumo lygius bei stebi akumuliatoriaus ir įrenginio įkrovos lygius.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lo">ຕົວຈັດການພະລັງງານ Xfce ຍັງມີປລັກອິນສຳລັບແຖບພາເນລຂອງ Xfce ແລະ LXDE ເພື່ອຄວບຄຸມລະດັບຄວາມສະຫວ່າງ LCD ແລະ ກວດສອບລະດັບການສາກຂອງແບັດເຕີຣີ ແລະ ອຸປະກອນ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Xfce 전원 관리자에서는 LCD 밝기를 조절하고 배터리와 장치 충전 상태를 감시하는 Xfce 및 LXDE용 플러그인도 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">Xfce ಪವರ್ ಮ್ಯಾನೇಜರ್ LCD ಬ್ರೈಟ್ನೆಸ್ ಮಟ್ಟವನ್ನು ನಿಯಂತ್ರಿಸಲು ಮತ್ತು ಬ್ಯಾಟರಿ ಮತ್ತು ಸಾಧನ ಚಾರ್ಜ್ ಮಟ್ಟವನ್ನು ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಣೆ ಮಾಡಲು Xfce ಮತ್ತು LXDE ಪ್ಯಾನೆಲ್ಗಳಿಗೆ ಸಹ ಒಂದು ಪ್ಲಗ್ಇನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы LCD экраны жарықтылығын басқару және батарея/құрылғылар заряд шамасын бақылау мүмкіндігін беретін Xfce және LXDE панельдері үшін плагинді ұсынады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Xfce-ის ენერგიის მმართველი ასევე მოგაწოდებთ დამატებას Xfce და LXDE პანელებისთვის, რომ მართოთ LCD-ის სიკაშკაშე და უყუროთ ელემენტისა და მოწყობილობების მუხტის დონეებს.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">また、Xfce パネル用と LXDE パネル用のプラグインも 2 種類提供しています。一つは LCD の輝度レベルを調整するもの、もう一つはバッテリやデバイスの充電レベルを監視するものです。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il gestore dell'energia di Xfce fornisce anche un componente aggiuntivo per il pannello di Xfce e di LXDE che permette di controllare la luminosità dello schermo e monitorare i livelli di carica della batteria del dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Manajer daya Xfce juga menyediakan plugin pada panel Xfce dan LXDE untuk mengontrol kecerahan layar dan memonitor sisa tenaga baterai dan level pengisian baterai.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hye">Xfce լիցքի կառավարիչը նաեւ մատակարարում է ներդրաւն Xfce եւ LXDE վահանակների համար, հեղուկաբիւրեղային ցուցասարքերի պայծառութեան մակարդակը կառավարելու, ինչպես նաեւ՝ հսկելու մարտկոցն ու սարքերի լիցքի մակարդակները։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hy_AM">Xfce լիցքի կառավարիչը նաեւ մատակարարում է ներդրաւն Xfce եւ LXDE վահանակների համար, հեղուկաբիւրեղային ցուցասարքերի պայծառութեան մակարդակը կառավարելու, ինչպես նաեւ՝ հսկելու մարտկոցն ու սարքերի լիցքի մակարդակները։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Xfce energiakezelő bővítményeket is biztosít az Xfce és az LXDE panelekhez az LCD fényességi szintjének vezérléséhez, illetve az akkumulátor és az eszközök töltöttségi szintjének figyelemmel követéséhez.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Xfce upravitelj energijom također pruža priključke za Xfce i LXDE ploče koji omogućavaju upravljanje svjetlinom LCD zaslona te praćenje korištenja i napunjenosti baterije uređaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מנהל צריכת חשמל Xfce מספק גם תוסף ללוחות של Xfce ושל LXDE כדי לשלוט ברמות בהירות LCD וגם כדי לעקוב אחר רמות טעינה של סוללה והתקן.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O xestor de enerxía do Xfce tamén fornece un engadido para os paneis Xfce e LXDE para o control dos niveis de brillo da pantalla e monitorización dos niveis de batería e dispositivos de carga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce fournit également un greffon pour les tableaux de bord Xfce et LXDE afin de contrôler le niveau de luminosité de l’écran LCD et de surveiller les niveaux de charge de la batterie et des périphériques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Xfce:n virranhallinta tarjoaa myös kaksi liitännäistä Xfce:n ja LXDE:n paneeleihin, yhden hallitsemaan näytön kirkkautta ja toisen laitteiden akkujen tilan seurantaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Xfce energia kudeatzaileak Xfce eta LXDE paneletarako, LCD distira-mailak kontrolatzeko eta bateriaren eta gailuaren karga-mailak kontrolatzeko plugin bat ere eskaintzen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Xfce vooluhalduri pistikprogramm on kasutusel nii Xfce kui LXDE ribal ning sellega saab kontrollida nii LCD ekraani eredust kui aku laetuse taset.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El gestor de energía de Xfce también proporciona un complemento para los paneles de Xfce y LXDE que permite controlar los niveles de brillo de la pantalla y monitorear los niveles de carga de la batería y de los dispositivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Xfce power manager also provides a plugin for the Xfce and LXDE panels to control LCD brightness levels and to monitor battery and device charge levels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_CA">Xfce power manager also provides a plugin for the Xfce and LXDE panels to control LCD brightness levels and to monitor battery and device charge levels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">Xfce power manager also provides a plugin for the Xfce and LXDE panels to control LCD brightness levels and to monitor battery and device charge levels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο διαχειριστής ρεύματος του Xfce παρέχει επίσης ένα πρόσθετο για τον έλεγχο της φωτεινότητας, της μπαταρίας και του επιπέδου φόρτισης των συσκευών για τα ταμπλό του Xfce και του LXDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Xfce-Energieverwaltung stellt ebenfalls ein Erweiterung für die Xfce- und die LXDE-Leiste zur Verfügung, um die Bildschirmhelligkeit zu steuern und um die Akkuladung und die Geräteladung zu überwachen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Xfce Strømstyringen tilbyder også et plugin til Xfce- og LXDE-panelerne, til at styre niveauet for LCD-lysstyrken, samt overvåger batteri og enhedernes ladeniveauer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Správce napájení pro Xfce také poskytuje zásuvný modul pro panely Xfce a LXDE pro ovládání úrovně jasu displejů LCD a pro sledování úrovní nabití baterie a zařízení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El gestor d'energia de Xfce també proporciona un connector per als panells de Xfce per controlar els nivells de brillantor LCD i per monitorar els nivells de la bateria i de càrrega del dispositiu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Xfce Power Manager също така включва и добавка за панелите на Xfce и LXDE, за контрол на яркостта на LCD екрана и наблюдение на нивата на заряд на батерията и зарядните устройства.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Кіраўнік сілкавання таксама прапануе ўбудову панэляў Xfce і LXDE для кіравання яркасцю LCD-дысплэяў і ўзроўнем зараду батарэі і прылад.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">El xestor d'enerxía Xfce también proporciona un plugin pa los paneles de Xfce ya LXDE, pa poder controlar los ñiveles de rellumu nes pantalles LCD ya la enerxía de la batería ya'l preséu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">كما يوفر مدير الطاقة اكسفس ﻻحقة لألواح اكسفس ولكسدي للسيطرة على مستويات سطوع الشاشة ومراقبة مستويات البطارية وجهاز الشحن.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">xfce4-power-manager-settings.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="624" height="351">https://docs.xfce.org/_media/xfce/xfce4-power-manager/xfpm-general.png</image>
      <caption>Screenshot of the Xfce Power Manager User Interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">Xfce 電源管理員使用者介面的螢幕截圖</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">Xfce 电源管理器用户界面屏幕截图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Ảnh chụp màn hình Giao diện người dùng Xfce Power Manager</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Знімок екрану інтерфейсу менеджера живлення Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ug">Xfce توك مەنبە باشقۇرغۇچنىڭ ئىشلەتكۈچى ئارايۈزىنىڭ ئېكران كەسمىسى</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Xfce Güç Yöneticisi Kullanıcı Arayüzünün ekran görüntüsü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="th">ภาพหน้าจอส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้ของระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Skärmdump av Xfce strömhanterare användargränssnittet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Слика заслона корисничког сучеља управника напајања ИксФЦЕ-а</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sq">Foto ekrani e Ndërfaqes së Përdoruesit të Përgjegjësit Xfce të Energjisë</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Posnetek zaslona uporabniškega vmesnika Xfce upravljalnika porabe energije</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Snímka používateľského rozhrania Správcu napájania Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Снимок экрана интерфейса Менеджера питания Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Captură de ecran a interfeței de utilizator a administratorului de energie Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Captura de ecrã da Interface de Utilizador do Gestor de Energia Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Captura de tela da interface de usuário do gerenciador de energia do Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Zrzut ekranu interfejsu użytkownika Menedżera zasilania Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Captura d'ecran de l'interfàcia utilizaire del gestionari d'alimentacion Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Schermafdruk van de gebruikersomgeving van Xfce Energiebeheerder</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Skjermbilde av brukergrensesnittet til Xfce Strømstyrer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Xfce maitinimo tvarkytuvės naudotojo sąsajos ekrano kopija</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lo">ພາບໜ້າຈໍຂອງສ່ວນຕິດຕໍ່ຜູ້ໃຊ້ຕົວຈັດການພະລັງງານ Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Xfce 전원 관리자 사용자 인터페이스 스크린샷</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы пайдаланушы интерфейсінің скриншоты</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Xfce-ის ენერგიის მმართველის ინტერფეისის ეკრანის ანაბეჭდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">Xfce 電源管理ユーザーインターフェイスのスクリーンショット</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Istantanea dell'interfaccia utente del gestore dell'energia di Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Képernyőkép az Xfce energiakezelő felhasználói felületéről</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">צילום מסך של ממשק משתמש מנהל חשמל Xfce </caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Captura de pantalla da interface de usuario de Xfce Power Manager</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Capture d’écran de l’interface utilisateur du gestionnaire d’énergie Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Kuvakaappaus Xfce:n virranhallinnan käyttöliittymästä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Xfce Energia-kudeatzailearen erabiltzaile-interfazearen pantaila-argazkia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Xfce vooluhalduri kasutajaliidese ekraanitõmmis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Captura de pantalla de la interfaz de usuario de Xfce Power Manager</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Screenshot of the Xfce Power Manager User Interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_CA">Screenshot of the Xfce Power Manager User Interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Στιγμιότυπο οθόνης του διαχειριστή ρεύματος Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Screenshot der Benutzeroberfläche der Xfce Energieverwaltung</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Skærmbillede af brugerfladen i Xfce Strømstyring</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Snímek rozhraní správce napájení</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Captura de pantalla de la interfície d'usuari del gestor d'energia del Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Екранна снимка на потребителският интерфейс на Управление на захранването на Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ast">Imaxe de la interfaz d'usuariu del xestor d'enerxía Xfce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لقطة شاشة من واجهة المستخدم لمدير طاقة Xfce</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.xfce.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/xfce/xfce4-power-manager</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/xfce/xfce4-power-manager/start</url>
  <url type="contact">https://docs.xfce.org/contribute/dev/start#communication_with_the_xfce_development_team</url>
  <update_contact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">xfce4-power-manager</translation>
  <project_group>Xfce</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>xfce4-power-manager</binary>
    <binary>xfce4-power-manager-settings</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.3.2" timestamp="1408573857">
      <description>
        <p>This development release mostly fixes bugs and introduces better support
        for icon-themes by reducing the device icons and using standard names for
        them. It also features updated translations. The panel plugin has been
        renamed to Power Manager Plugin.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.3.1" timestamp="1407741245">
      <description>
        <p>This development release fixes bugs with suspend and hibernate. It also
        improves the panel-plugin, incorporating the functionality of the (now
        dropped) brightness panel-plugin. A new popup notification was added to
        account for keyboard brightness changes and the Power Manager now also
        controls the X11 blank times.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.3.0" timestamp="1401646266">
      <description>
        <p>This development release introduces a lot of new features, among them
        suspending/hibernation without systemd and UPower&gt;=0.99. It allows for
        individual control of systemd-inhibition, a new panel plugin to monitor
        battery and device charge levels replaces the trayicon. The settings dialog
        has been completely restructured for better oversight and many open bugs
        have been fixed and translations have been updated.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.0" timestamp="1335645654">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes compilation problems, a memory leak and
        a few other minor bugs. Furthermore it provides updated translations.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
