<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>xfce4-clipman.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">Clipman 剪贴板管理器</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ur">کلپ مین</name>
  <name xml:lang="ur_PK">کلپ مین</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Буфер обміну</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">Clipman چاپلاش تاختىسى باشقۇرغۇچ</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">คลิปแมน</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Секач</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Менеджер буфера обмена Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Menedżer schowka</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Klembordbeheer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Starpliktuve</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="lo">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Klippispjald</name>
  <name xml:lang="ie">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="hye">Սեղմամարդ</name>
  <name xml:lang="hy_AM">Սեղմամարդ</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_CA">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_AU">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Zwischenablage</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Správce schránky</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Clipman</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">Clipman</name>
  <summary>Clipboard manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">剪貼簿管理員</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">剪贴板管理器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Trình quản lý bộ nhớ đệm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ur">کلپ بورڈ منیجر</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ur_PK">کلپ بورڈ منیجر</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Керування буфером обміну</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ug">چاپلاش تاختىسىنى باشقۇرغۇچ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Pano yöneticisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">เครื่องมือจัดการคลิปบอร์ด</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Urklippshanterare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Управник исечака</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Përgjegjës të papastre</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik odložišča Clipman</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správca schránky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Менеджер буфера обмена</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Gestionar clipboard</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de área de transferência</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Gerenciador de área de transferência</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządza skopiowanymi elementami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Gestionari de quichapapièrs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Klembordbeheer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Utklippsbehandler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Pengurus papan keratan</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Starpliktuves pārvaldnieks</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Iškarpinės tvarkytuvė</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lo">ຕົວຈັດການຄລິບບອດ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">클립보드 관리자</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Алмасу буферін басқарушысы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ბუფერის მმართველი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">クリップボードマネージャーです</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore degli appunti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Manajer papan klip</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hye">Սեղմատախտակի կառավարիչ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Vágólapkezelő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Upravitelj međuspremnika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מנהל לוח אטיב</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xestor do portapapeis</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de presse-papiers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Leikepöydän hallinta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Arbel kudeatzailea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Lõikepuhvri haldur</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor del portapapeles</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Clipboard manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_CA">Clipboard manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Διαχειριστής προχείρου</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Zwischenablageverwaltung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Udklipsholderhåndtering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Správce schránky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor del porta-retalls</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Мениджър на системният буфер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Кіраўнік буфера абмену</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Xestor del cartafueyu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مدير الحافظة</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Clipboard Manager provided as a panel plugin for Xfce and as a standalone
      application running in the notification area. It keeps a history of text
      and images of content copied to the clipboard. It also has a feature to
      execute actions on specific text selection by matching them against
      regexes.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">剪貼簿管理員提供一個 Xfce 的面板外掛程式與在通知區域中單獨執行的應用程式。它保留了文字及圖片被複製到剪貼簿的歷史。它也有被選擇的文字符合正則表達式時可執行的功能。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">剪贴板管理器是一个 Xfce 的面板插件，它在通知区域中单独执行。它保留了文字及图片被复制到剪贴板的历史。它也有在被选择的文字符合正则表达式时执行的功能。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Trình quản lí bộ đệm được cung cấp dưới dạng một plugin thanh tác vụ hoặc một chương trình riêng chạy trong vùng thông báo. Nó lưu trữ lịch sử sao chép các văn bản và hình ảnh. Trình quản lí cũng có tính năng thực hiện các lệnh khác nhau lên các mục được chọn bằng cách so sánh chúng với các biểu thức chính quy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Керівник буфера обміну надається як втулка для панелі Xfce і як окрема програма, що запускається в області сповіщень. Тут зберігається історія скопійованого в буфер обміну тексту, зображень  та іншого вмісту. Також має функцію виконання дій для виділення специфічного тексту зіставивши його з певним регулярним виразом.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ug">چاپلاش تاختىسى باشقۇرغۇچ Xfce نىڭ كۆزنەكچە قىستۇرمىسى، ئۇ ئۇقتۇرۇش رايونىدا ئايرىم ئىجرا قىلىنىدۇ. ئۇ تېكىست ۋە سۈرەتنىڭ چاپلاش تاختىسىغا كۆچۈرۈلۈش تارىخىنى ساقلاپ قالىدۇ. ئۇنىڭ يەنە تاللانغان تېكىست مۇنتىزىم ئىپادىگە ماس كەلگەندە مەشغۇلات ئىجرا قىلىش ئىقتىدارى بار.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Pano Yöneticisi Xfce için bir panel eklentisi olarak ve bildirim alanında kendi başına çalışan bir uygulama olarak sunulmaktadır. Panoya kopyalanan metin ve resimlerin geçmişini saklar. Ayrıca belirli metin seçimleri üzerinde onları düzenli ifadelerle eşleştirip eylemler çalıştırma özelliği de vardır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">เครื่องมือจัดการคลิปบอร์ด มีทั้งในรูปปลั๊กอินสำหรับพาเนลของ Xfce และในรูปโปรแกรมโดดที่ทำงานในพื้นที่แจ้งเหตุ โปรแกรมนี้จะเก็บประวัติของเนื้อหาข้อความและรูปภาพที่มีการคัดลอกลงในคลิปบอร์ด นอกจากนี้ ยังสามารถเรียกการกระทำกับข้อความบางรูปแบบที่เลือกได้ โดยตรวจสอบรูปแบบด้วยนิพจน์เรกิวลาร์</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Urklippshanteraren tillhandahålls som ett panelinsticksprogram och som ett fristående program som körs i meddelandefältet. Det sparar en historik av text och bilder från innehåll som kopierats till urklipp. Det har också en funktion för att utföra åtgärder på specifika textmarkeringar genom att matcha dem mot regexes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник исечака у виду прикључка полице ИксФЦЕ-а и као самосталан програм који ради у обавештајној области. Бележи садржаје писма и слика умноженог у оставу исечака. Такође, може да извршава дејства над изабраним писмом његовим упоређивањем са регуларним изразима.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Përgjegjës të Papastre dhënë si një shtojcë paneli për Xfce-në dhe si aplikacion më vete që xhiron te zona e njoftimeve. Mban një historik teksti dhe figurash të lëndës së kopjuar te e papastra. Përmban gjithashtu një veçori për të ekzekutuar veprime në rast përzgjedhje teksti të caktuar duke e përputhur këtë me shprehje të rregullta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik odložišča Clipman je na voljo kot vtičnik za Xfce pano ali kot samostojen program, ki  deluje v področju za obvestila. Shranjuje zgodovino tekstovnih in slikovnih vsebin, ki so bile kopirane na odložišče. Ima tudi funkcijo izvajanja dejanj za določen izbor teksta, ki jih primerja z regularnimi izrazi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Správca schránky vo forme zásuvného modulu panela XFCE a ako samostatná aplikácia spustená v informačnej oblasti. Uchováva históriu obsahu textu a obrázkov kopírovaných do schránky. Poskytuje aj možnosť spúšťania akcií na výbere textu, ktorý zodpovedá regulárnym výrazom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Менеджер буфера обмена может быть модулем для панели Xfce и самостоятельным приложением, выполняемым в области уведомления. Менеджер хранит историю копированного в буфер обмена текста и изображений. Имеется возможность выполнения действий над выбранным текстом, удовлетворяющим заданным регулярным выражениям.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Gestionarul de clipboard oferit ca modul de panou pentru Xfce și ca aplicație autonomă care rulează în zona de notificare. Acesta păstrează un istoric al conținutului de text și imagini copiat în clipboard. De asemenea, are o caracteristică de a executa acțiuni pe selecții de text specifice prin potrivirea acestora cu expresii regulate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Gestor da área de transferência fornecido como um plugin para o painel Xfce e como uma aplicação própria inserida na área de notificação. Mantém um histórico de texto e imagens do conteúdo copiado para a área de transferência. Tem também uma funcionalidade para executar ações sobre a seleção de texto específico, combinando-as com expressões regulares.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Gerenciador de área de transferência fornecido como um plugin de painel para o Xfce e como um aplicativo independente em execução na área de notificação. Ele mantém um histórico de texto e imagens de conteúdos copiados para a área de transferência. Ele também possui um recurso para executar ações sobre a seleção de texto específico, combinando-os contra expressões regulares</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Menedżer schowka umieszczony jako wtyczka dla panelu Xfce i jako samodzielny program działający w obszarze powiadomień. Przechowuje historię tekstu i obrazów z treści skopiowanych do schowka. Ma również funkcję wykonywania czynności na konkretnie zaznaczonym tekście, dopasowując je do wyrażeń regularnych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Lo gestionari de quichapapièrs es provesit coma plugin de panèl per Xfce e coma aplicacion autonòma foncionant dins la zòna de notificacion. Consèrva un istoric del tèxt e dels imatges del contengut copiat dins lo quichapapièrs. Tanben a una foncionalitat per executar d'accions sus una seleccion de tèxt especifica en las fasent correspondre a d'expressions regularas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Klembordbeheer als invoegsel voor de werkbalk van Xfce en als een op zichzelf staande toepassing die draait in het meldvak. Hij houdt een geschiedenis bij van tekst en afbeeldingen die zijn gekopieerd naar het klembord. Hij heeft ook een functie waarmee acties kunnen worden uitgevoerd op een bepaalde tekstselectie, door deze af te zetten tegen regexes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Utklippstavlebehandleren tilbys som et paneltillegg for Xfce og som frittstående program kjørende i varslingsområdet. Det tar vare på historikk og tekst fra bilder og innhold som kopieres til utklippstavlen. Det har også den egenskapen at det utfører handlinger på gitt tekst ved å jamføre dem mot regulære uttrykk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Pengurus Papan Keratan disediakan sebagai pemalam panel untuk Xfce dan sebagai aplikasi berdiri-sendiri yang berjalan di dalam kawasan pemberitahuan. Ia menyimpan sejarah teks dan imej kandungan yang disalin ke dalam papan keratan. ia juga mempunyai fitur untuk lakukan tindakan pada pemilihan teks tertentu dengan memadan ia dengan regex.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Iškarpinės tvarkytuvė pateikiama kaip Xfce skydelio įskiepis bei kaip atskira, pranešimų srityje vykdoma, programa. Ji saugo, į iškarpinę nukopijuoto turinio teksto ir paveikslų, žurnalą. Programoje taip pat yra galimybė, esant tam tikro teksto žymėjimui, vykdyti veiksmus, atitinkančius tam tikrus reguliariuosius reiškinius.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lo">ຕົວຈັດການຄລິບບອດທີ່ມີໃຫ້ໃນຮູບແບບປລັກອິນແຜງຄວບຄຸມສຳລັບ Xfce ແລະ ເປັນແອັບພລິເຄຊັນທີ່ເຮັດວຽກດ້ວຍຕົວເອງໃນສ່ວນແຈ້ງເຕືອນ. ມັນເຮັດໜ້າທີ່ເກັບປະຫວັດຂໍ້ຄວາມ ແລະ ຮູບພາບທີ່ຖືກສຳເນົາໄວ້ໃນຄລິບບອດ. ນອກຈາກນີ້ ຍັງມີຄຸນສົມບັດໃນການສັ່ງການກັບຂໍ້ຄວາມທີ່ເລືອກໂດຍການຈັບຄູ່ກັບນິພົດປົກກະຕິ (regexes).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">클립보드 관리자는 Xfce 패널 플러그인이며, 알림 영역에서 독립적으로 실행하는 형태로 제공합니다. 이 관리자는 텍스트와 이미지 내용을 클립보드에 복사한 상태를 유지해줍니다. 정규표현식에 일치하는 특정 텍스트를 선택하는 기능도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Алмасу буфері басқарушысы Xfce үшін панель плагині және хабарламалар аймағындар орындалатын бөлек жеке қолданба ретінде келеді. Ол алмасу буферіне көшірілген құраманың мәтін және суреттер тарихын сақтайды. Сонымен қатар, ол көрсетілген тұрақты өрнектерге сай келетін мәтін табылған кезде белгіленген әрекетттерді орындай алады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">クリップボードマネージャーは Xfce 用のパネルプラグインまたは通知エリア内で動作する独立したプリケーションとして提供されています。クリップボードにコピーされた文字列や画像の履歴を記憶し、選択した文字列に対して正規表現がマッチした場合に指定されたアクションを実行できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Gestore degli appunti fornito come componente aggiuntivo del pannello di Xfce e come un'applicazione indipendente in esecuzione nell'area di notifica. Mantiene la cronologia dei testi ed immagini copiati negli appunti. Consente anche di eseguire specifiche azioni sui testi in base ad espressioni regolari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Manajer Papan Klip disediakan sebagai panel pengaya untuk Xfce dan sebagai aplikasi mandiri yang berjalan di area notifikasi. Ini menyimpan riwayat teks dan gambar konten yang disalin ke papan klip. Ini juga memiliki fitur untuk melakukan tindakan pada pemilihan teks tertentu dengan mencocokkannya dengan regex.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hye">Սեղմատախտակի կառավարիչը մատակարարուել է որպէս Xfce֊ի ներդրաւն, եւ որպէս ծանուցումների դաշտում գործող ինքնավար յաւելուած։ Այդ պահում է գրոյթի եւ պատկերների պատմութիւնը սեղմատախտակում պատճէնուած։ Այդ արդէն ունի իւրահատկութիւն յատուկ գրոյթային ընտրութեան գործողութիւնների աշխատեցման, ըստ regex֊ների նմանակումով։</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A vágólapkezelőz panelkiegészítőként szállítja az Xfce, és különálló alkalmazásként az értesítési területen. Megjegyzi a vágólapra másolt szövegek és képek előzményeit. Olyan funkciója is van, amely műveleteket végez, ha a szövegkiválasztások reguláris kifejezésekre illeszkednek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Clipboard Manager odnosno Upravitelj međuspremnikom postoji kao dodatak za ploču ili kao samostalna aplikacija koja se izvodi u području obavijesti. Čuva povijest teksta i slika kopiranih u međuspremnik. Uz to pruža mogućnost izvođenja akcija nad određenim tekstom uspoređujeći ga s regexom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מנהל לוח אטיב מסופק כתוסף פאנל ל-Xfce וכתוכנה עצמאית הפועלת באיזור ההודעות. הוא שומר היסטוריה של טקסט ותמונות של תוכן המועתקות ללוח האטיב. יש לו גם מאפיין המאפשר פעולות על בחירת טקסט מסוימת ע"י השוואתן כנגד ביטויים רגולרים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Xestor de portapapeis fornecido como un engadido de panel para o Xfce e como aplicación autónoma que se executa na zona de notificación. Mantén un historial de texto e imaxes de contido copiados no portapapeis. Tamén ten unha función para executar accións sobre a selección de texto específica, combinándoas con expresións regulares.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le Gestionnaire de presse-papiers fournit un greffon pour le tableau de bord Xfce et une application autonome qui fonctionne dans la zone de notification. Il conserve un historique du texte et des images du contenu copié dans le presse-papiers. Il dispose aussi d’une fonctionnalité pour exécuter des actions sur une sélection de texte spécifique au travers d’expressions régulières.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Arbel kudeatzailea Xfce paneleko plugin bezala eta aplikazio independente bezala hornituta, Arbelera kopiatutako testu eta irudien edukien historia gordetzen du. Ekintzak exekutatzeko aukera ematen du ere hautatutako testua adierazpen erregularrekin bat datorrenean.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Lõikepuhvri haldur on olemas nii riba jaoks mõeldud pistikprogrammina, kui eraldi rakendusena, mis töötab teatede ribal. Ta salvestab lõikepuhvrisse kopeeritud teksti ja piltide ajaloo. Lisaks on võimalik valitud teksti võrdlemisel etteantud regulaaravaldisega käivitada soovitud toiminguid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El gestor del portapapeles se proporciona como un complemento para el panel de Xfce y como una aplicación independiente que se ejecuta en el área de notificación. Mantiene un historial de los textos y las imágenes copiados en el portapapeles. También tiene una función para ejecutar acciones en una selección específica de texto mediante la comparación con expresiones regulares.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Clipboard Manager is provided as a panel plugin for Xfce and as a standalone application running in the notification area. It keeps a history of text and images of content copied to the clipboard. It also has a feature to execute actions on specific text selection by matching them against regexes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_CA">Clipboard Manager provided as a panel plugin for Xfce and as a standalone application running in the notification area. It keeps a history of text and images of content copied to the clipboard. It also has a feature to execute actions on specific text selection by matching them against regexes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο διαχειριστής προχείρου παρέχεται ως πρόσθετο στο ταμπλό του Xfce και λειτουργεί σαν αυτόνομη εφαρμογή στην περιοχή ειδοποιήσεων. Διατηρεί το ιστορικό κειμένου και εικόνων που έχουν αντιγραφεί στο πρόχειρο. Διαθέτει επίσης δυνατότητα εκτέλεσης ενεργειών σε συγκεκριμένη επιλογή του κειμένου και την αντιστοίχισή τους με κανονικές εκφράσεις.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Zwischenablageverwaltung, bereitgestellt als eine Leistenerweiterung für Xfce und als eine alleinstehende Anwendung, die im Benachrichtigungsfeld läuft. Es enthält einen Verlauf von Text und Bildern vom Inhalt der in die Zwischenablage kopiert wurde. Es hat auch eine Funktion, um Aktionen an bestimmten ausgewählten Texten durch Vergleiche gegen reguläre Ausdrücke auszuführen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Udklipsholderhåndtering tilbydes som et panelplugin til Xfce, og som et enkeltstående program som kører i underretningsområdet. Den bevarer en historik over tekst og billeder fra indhold som er kopieret i udklipsholderen. Den kan også køre handlinger på særligt valgte tekster ved at matche dem mod regulære udtryk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Správce schránky poskytovaný jako zásuvný modul panelu pro Xfce a jako samostatná aplikace spuštěná v oznamovací oblasti. Udržuje historii textu a obrázků obsahu zkopírovaného do schránky.  Také má funkci ke spouštění akcí po označení textu odpovídajícímu regulárnímu výrazu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El gestor del porta-retalls es proporciona com a connector del panell per a Xfce i com a aplicació autònoma que s'executa a l'àrea de notificació. Manté un historial de text i imatges de contingut copiats al porta-retalls. També té una característica per executar accions en una selecció de text específica fent-les coincidir amb execucions regulars.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Clipboard Manager представлява добавка за панела на Xfce и като самостоятелно приложение работи в областта за уведомяване. Той съхранява историята на текста и изображенията от съдържанието, копирани в системният буфер. Той също така има функция да изпълнява действие по подбор на текст, като го сравнява с регулярен израз.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Кіраўнік буфера абмену можа быць як убудовай для панэлі Xfce, так і самастойнай праграмай для прасторы апавяшчэнняў. Ён захоўвае гісторыю скапіяваных у буфер абмену тэксту і выяў. Ёсць магчымасць выконваць дзеянні з абраным тэкстам паводле рэгулярных выразаў.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">El xestor de cartafueyu apúrrese como un complementu del panel pa Xfce y como aplicación independiente executándose na estaya de notificaciones. Caltien una historia de testu ya semeyes copiada al cartafueyu. Tamién tien una carauterística pa executar les aiciones na esbilla d etestu específicu y concasales colos rexistros.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/panel-plugins/clipman/clipman-menu.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://docs.xfce.org/panel-plugins/xfce4-clipman-plugin/start</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/panel-plugins/xfce4-clipman-plugin</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/panel-plugins/xfce4-clipman-plugin/start</url>
  <updatecontact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</updatecontact>
  <project_group>XFCE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>xfce4-clipman</binary>
    <binary>xfce4-clipman-settings</binary>
    <binary>xfce4-popup-clipman</binary>
  </provides>
  <!--
  <releases>
    <release version="0.9.0" timestamp="1231974000">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>A rewrite to make it more user-friendly and introduce image support. Work done by David Collins</li>
          <li>Drop the repetitive timeout against a callback/signal to check for clipboard changes.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
-->
</component>
